Shochiku Films
Good Morning
Screenplay by
Kogo Noda and Yasujiro Ozu
Produced by Shizuo Yamanouchi
Cinematography by Yuharu Atsuta
Art Direction by Tatsuo Hamada
Cast:
Keiji Sada as Heiichiro Fukui
Yoshiko Kuga as Setsuko Arita
Chishu Ryu as Keitaro Hayashi
Kuniko Miyake as Tamiko
Haruko Sugimura as Kikue Haraguchi
Koji Shitara as Minoru
Masahiko Shimazu as lsamu
Directed by Yasujiro Ozu
Hey?
Hey, nudge me again
- See?
- Let me
See?
You're rubbish
Oi, what's wrong? Come on
What's up? Come on
Come on
- Mrs Okubo?
- Oh, thank you
- Here you go
- Thanks so much
- That spinach looks good
- lt's so expensive. 20 yen
- Really? l can't even afford spinach nowadays
- l know
Listen...
l heard something strange.
Our women's group fees weren't paid
But we paid up, didn't we?
l know, but l ran into the chairwoman
and she said we hadn't paid
But l definitely paid
So did l!
How odd! lt doesn't make sense
lt's very odd
- Although, thinking about it...
- What?
Didn't her next doorjust buy
a washing machine?
Yes, but in monthly instalments
But isn't that strange about our fees?
Mrs Okubo?
- That's her
- Yes?
- Here's the women's group bulletin board
- Thank you
- Welcome home
- Hello
You're back early
What's wrong with you?
Hi...
Where are you offto?
Better not be next door!
No, l'm going to study
l don't know what to do with him.
All he cares about is television
- lt's the sumo season, isn't it?
- That's right
- Listen...
- What?
What happened the other day?
- Well, it's very strange
- Why?
Kozo, l'm offover there
Mum, will you get me
another pair of pants?
What's the matter with you?
An upset stomach?
Why did you soil your pants?
You do this every day
l didn't buy a washing machine
just for your pants!
Mum...
Just give me a clean pair
Watching sumo is all right...
...but they never learn anything
worthwhile over there
You're absolutely right
We should have nothing
to do with them
The husband and wife laze around
in pyjamas all day long
She used to work in a cabaret in lkebukuro
So she's that kind ofwoman, is she?
- l should be off
- How much is the sauce, though?
Sort it out later.
l owe you money, too
- Really?
- Bye!
Hiya!
Come on in
- ls Minoru here yet?
- Not yet
Hailing from Hokkaido, Kitabayama
is well known for his fighting spirit
His opponent on the right
is Togashi from Yamagata...
Wakanohana's looking good today
Who do you think will win, Ko?
That's easy. lsn't it?
Course! He's got a superb throw
You reckon?
Help yourself
lt's time to leave, dear
lsn't the boy from next door coming?
Shall we call him?
- Hey, Minoru?
- Minoru!
- Come over
- What's the matter? Hurry up
- Just going out!
- l'm just going out!
Where are you going?
To study English
- And lsamu?
- Me too
You're not watching TV again, are you?
Don't be going next door
Silly boys!
Mrs Hayashi?
Spare a moment?
This might seem like a strange question...
...but did you give our women's group fees
to the chairwoman?
Yes, about 10 days ago, l think
l see. l thought so
But she says she hasn't received them yet
Why's that?
Not only that, l heard that Mrs Haraguchi
just bought a washing machine
But she wouldn't...
l know. But Mrs Okubo says
she gave the fees to you
Yes, she did, definitely.
Shall l ask the chairwoman?
But ifshe says
she hasn't received them yet...
l definitely gave them to her
Ofcourse you did.
You wouldn't forget something like that
So how could this have happened?
- Well...
- This is distressing
Here is our very popular hero,
Wakahichibu...
...as he performs
the salt ceremony in the ring
And now he faces his opponent
in this title match...
Good day to...
You here again, Kozo?
Don't you ever listen?
Good day
Sorry my son's always round here
bothering you
What about your English lessons?
What about you, Minoru?
And Zen, your mother will scold you, too
- They must be such a nuisance for you
- l don't mind at all
All right, time to go home.
Come on, you lot
l'm not going.
l've finished my English homework
What? l'll tell your mother.
Come on!
Thank you so much
- Goodbye
Say hello to your teacher
from "big sister"
- "Big sister"? You mean from you?
- Who else do you think?
Bye
What took you so long?
What about your English lessons?
Hello. Anybody home?
Yes, who is it?
l just spoke with Mrs Tomizawa...
...and told her l handed over our fees
more than a week ago
All this fuss makes me feel
that l'm somehow responsible
l'm really sorry
Don't worry about it, Mrs Hayashi
We know it's not your fault.
You didn't have to come to tell me that
But l...
lt's only because Mrs Tomizawa
mentioned a washing machine...
...that l began to wonder what happened
- That isn't what concerns me, though
- Well, ofcourse it shouldn't
But why hasn't the chairwoman
received the fees yet?
This is all just so unpleasant for you,
isn't it?
l'll ask Mrs Haraguchi.
l feel it's my responsibility
Oh, l wouldn't bother with that.
lt would only trouble her
But l...
You don't have to worry.
We all trust you
Time will tell who's to blame.
Don't you worry yourself
lt's a whodunit,
just like in that film, remember?
- But l...
- Don't worry about it
What are you up to?
- Have you finished that translation yet?
- l'm working on it
Are you two done?
Go on and read it to me
Translate the meaning
'My sister is three years old.
She is younger than l am.'
No, that's a bit different
How about you, Kozo?
l mean translate it
What does it mean?
Try to translate it
Go on
- Sorry, it's second nature now
- What is?
We all do it now.
Nudge me here again
Silly lad!
- Are you all right?
- Course l am
What is it?
l've been eating pumice powder
every day
- Who told you to do something daft like that?
- Zen's dad
lt doesn't help, you know.
He was only teasing you
But it's true. lsn't it?
His dad's really good at it
Did you call me?
- No
- Really?
- l'm back
Minoru?
Why don't you ever listen to a word l say?
You were next door again
So what? We just went to watch TV
But l told you no
- Then buy us a TV
- Absolutely not
Buy us a TV!
No. Now eat your supper
Here
Go ahead
What? Dried fish and miso soup again?
Don't complain
Are you going to complain, too, lsamu?
No, l won't
Welcome home
Evening
- You came together?
- Yes, from the station
- Welcome home
- We're having dried fish again, Dad
lsamu! You said you wouldn't complain
Hi, boys
- The pork soup tastes good, Auntie
- ls it? Good
- We get it every night, though
- For you
Auntie?
What is it?
My teacher said that
the translation will be ready tomorrow
All right
How did Wakanohana do today?
Dunno. We don't have a TV set
Mum, buy us a TV
No way
What about the radio?
- lt has to be a TV
- Can't see nothing on the radio
- Buy us a TV set, Mum
- Buy us a TV set!
l said no and l mean no
Would you like a bath?
You filled the tub already?
Who spilled toothpaste in the bathroom?
- Not me
- Me neither
Who was it then?
You two, really...
l don't know
Me neither
- Good morning, sir
Morning
Hey, don't dawdle on the way
Yes, sir!
Hey...ready?
That's rubbish!
Good one. Now nudge me
Let me do it
How about that?
You're really good at it, Zen.
Do you eat sweet potatoes?
No!
- Did you call me?
- No
What is it?
Listen, l'm going to Kameido.
Want me to pick up some cakes?
Yes, get some
Oh, it's such a lovely day
Yes?
- Oh, morning
- Morning
You're early
- Have you finished the translations?
- l've had to look up every technical term
l'm about 70% through
My office needs it by today
- How's the rest going?
- Let me see
Do you want to take this, then?
- l'll finish the rest today
- Today for sure?
Yeah
Sis, Setsuko's here
Welcome. l thought it was you
- Good morning
- Morning. Offto work already?
Yes. Sorry to have to bother your brother
Not at all, it's extra income
My company went bankrupt,
so l'll do just about anything
Thanks for what you've done. Goodbye
Oh, Setsuko?
There's talk about having
our class reunion at Chinzanso Restaurant
- Tell your sister
- Yes, l will. Bye
- See you soon
- Thank you
Bye
Setsuko's a nice girl
Wouldn't it be nice ifshe married you?
You're kidding? l'm out of a job
That's not a problem.
You'll find another one
What about yourjob? How are sales?
- l may sell another Austin today
- Really? That's great
Hello? Anybody home?
- Hello?
- Yes?
Oh, Mrs Haraguchi.
You should've come through the front
Never mind that.
Can l have a word?
Please come in. What is it?
lt's a mess, but please come in
All right
Please...
So you know we bought
a washing machine?
Yes, l heard
l'd love one, too, but we can't afford it yet
You should just buy one ifyou want one.
lt's your money, why worry about it?
We're not rich like you
But we bought one
without making a big fuss about it
My mother's making money, too, you know
We don't need to steal
the women's group fees
The very idea of it. How insulting!
Who said such a thing?
Don't pretend you don't know.
You should ask yourselfthat question
- What?
- l'm fastidious by nature
l'd never steal a thing
Such hateful gossip.
l'm going to quit my post
l've simply been made a fool of
l'm afraid l don't understand
The women's group fees!
You're the treasurer, aren't you?
What about it?
You said you gave me the fees...
...so now l look like a thief
l'll give it you straight,
l've received nothing
Oh? l took them over, l'm sure
- When?
- The 28th of last month
- l received nothing
- But l delivered them
No, l received nothing!
But l definitely gave them to your mother
Then she would have given them to me
l wouldn't know. You should ask her
- Hello?
- Yes?
Excuse me a moment
Good day.
Are you the mistress ofthe house?
Right, then...
l have rubber strings, toothbrushes...
...pencils or brushes?
We have everything we need
Really? Everything?
That's what everybody says
How about a pencil?
Quiet round here, isn't it?
Sorry, but we don't need anything
Nothing? Don't say that.
Come on, buy a pencil
lt sharpens well
How about you, madam?
Want a pencil?
l have pencils, rubber strings,
toothbrushes, brushes?
Hey, madam! Madam?
Oh, well, whatever...
- Mother...
- What's all the fuss?
- Has a salesman called by?
- Haven't seen one
Will you talk to him if he calls round?
He's awful
Why? What happened?
- Anybody home?
- See? That's him
Yes, who is it?
Good day to you
l have rubber strings, toothbrushes, pencils
And scrubbing brushes
No, thanks
Don't you need a pencil? lt sharpens well
Don't say that to me. Buy a pencil
Can l sharpen it first and see?
Ofcourse, sharpen it. Go ahead, here
Never mind.
l'll sharpen it with my own knife
l've got cotton, too, madam. Want some?
No, thanks
Give me the pencil, then
That's sharp
How much are the toothbrushes?
50 yen
That's expensive. Too expensive!
What's the matter? You leaving?
Come again
Shut the door!
- ls he gone?
- Yes, he even left a pencil. See?
- No one stands a chance against you
- Can't be a coward and be a midwife
Listen, Mother, you didn't by any chance
receive the women's group fees, did you?
l would have given them to you
- That's right
- Ofcourse
Mrs Hayashi swears she paid you
the end of last month
l received nothing
What is it?
Hold on a minute
ls this it?
Yes, it is!
Why didn't you hand it to me?
Well, l...
Well, what?
Thanks to you, l can't go anywhere
without feeling ashamed
l'm the chairwoman,
l get blamed for everything
You're so forgetful
Why don't you go to Mt Narayama
with all the other dying old folk?
l just feel so angry!
l've been humiliated for no reason.
And by a senile old woman!
lt's really more than l can take!
Always fussing
Thinks she managed to grow up
all by herself
She drives me crazy
And her good-for-nothing husband
Thinks she's the bee's knees
And bearing a son like that
The cheek of her!
lt's me again
So sorry about earlier
l'm so sorry
My mother is terrible
She just told me she received the fees
l don't think l can apologise enough
l'm dreadfully sorry
Well, now that you realise, it's all right
l'm truly sorry.
l feel like crawling into a hole
Please forget what l said earlier
Very well. lt's all water under the bridge
- Really?
- Ofcourse
Oh, l'm so glad. Thanks
Don't tell anybody, will you?
You know how people gossip
No, l won't
Thanks again. Bye
Mrs Haraguchi?
- Come and look at these
- What is it?
lt's an alarm. The patent's pending
ln the case of a burglary or fire,
you just push this...
...and it can be heard 200 metres away
- A burglar alarm?
- Yes. lt deters pushy salesmen, too
lfonly you'd come sooner!
Did that fellow show up?
l had to buy pencils. Rubber bands, too
The police recommend this device
against those types ofsalesmen
Would you like one, madam?
Well, shall l buy one?
- How about your place?
- l have something even better
- You do?
- My mother
Nothing gets through her!
- What a lovely day
- lt certainly is
UKlYO RESTAURANT
- l'm done
- All right. One more!
Coming!
lt's so cold
- Where've you been?
- l bought this when l went out
Tomorrow's races?
Are you really into that?
How about the third race?
No good. Not a chance. Not worth it
- No?
- No
- How about the other way?
- No way
Here you are
You think so?
Give us another one
- Get one more
- All right
- Welcome
- Hello
Did l leave my gloves here?
Have you seen any gloves?
No, l haven't
All right
- Mr Hayashi...
- Oh, hello
Come and have a seat
Come and sit down
Give me some stew
- Here
- Thanks
Here you are
Where were you today?
Well, l have no prospects...
...but l still have to eat
Here, thanks
When is it for you?
Here you are
Retirement. l'm talking about retirement
lt's awful. lt's like being killed slowly
The companies think we don't need to eat
after we retire
But l eat and drink
My wife gives me a hard time,
but l just can't find a job
l'm stuck in a rut
There's no place under the sky to hide
lt's so awful
What about your pension, Mr Tomizawa?
No, no way, the company's too smart
They won't pay out much
For 30 years, come rain or shine...
...riding in jam-packed trains...
lt's all for nothing. Nothing
Mr Tomizawa...
Mr Tomizawa?
Leave me alone
Give us some potato cake
What are you doing? You're not eating
Not eating!
No? Fine
lt's no fun!
You're being awful. Just behave!
You're being stingy
You can go hungry, for all l care!
What about you, lsamu?
l won't eat
Do as you please
Silly boys. How long are you
going to keep this up?
Come here, lsamu
lsamu!
l'm not coming
Minoru, why are you being
so unreasonable? l'll tell your father
l don't care. l'm not afraid
That's your father now
lt's your father
Welcome home
- lt's cold out, isn't it?
- Yeah
l ran into Mr Tomizawa near the station
- He was fairly drunk
- Really?
- What's going on here?
- They're being awkward
- Why?
- They won't listen to a word l say
What?
l've told them not to, but they insist
on going next door to watch TV
So, buy us one, then!
They went next door
instead of English class again today
They're driving me up the wall
Then buy us a TV set!
Buy us one!
- No way
- Then we'll just go next door and watch
Me, too
You're being so stubborn!
l don't care. You're the stubborn one!
We only go there
because we don't have a TV at home!
We wouldn't go ifwe had one!
- Quiet!
- Stop it, or your father will scold you
l'm not afraid!
- l said quiet
- l won't. l don't have to
Look here!
- What did you say?
- Let me go! Let go!
You talk too much.
When l tell you to stop, you stop!
l didn't say anything
Creating a fuss over such a small thing,
you sound like a woman!
Children shouldn't answer back,
so just be quiet!
See? Now you've been scolded
l don't care. l want a TV
Stop answering back
Grown-ups talk all the time
"Hello. Good morning. Good evening.
Have a good day."
ldiot!
"How far is it? Just a little way.
ls that so?"
Just a lot oftalk. "l see, l see."
Forget it!
Silence! Be quiet!
Boys shouldn't prattle on
Be quiet
Fine. l'll be silent for days, then
Oh, l'd certainly appreciate that
- For 100 days
- Don't you start
No more talking
Come on, lsamu
- Right!
- What are we going to do with them?
Don't ever speak, lsamu
No matter what they say
You understand? l mean it
- Don't talk, whatever happens
- Outdoors, too?
Yes, l'll test you...
- Good
- My go!
- Okay?
- Okay
- This means l can talk, okay?
Farting's allowed
- l'm home
- Welcome back
You're late
Listen, Miss Fukui said
your class reunion may be at Chinzanso
- Really? Were you over there?
- Yes, just now
- Where are the boys?
- ln their room
Okay
Good, good. Studying hard?
Do you want some cakes?
They're really tasty
See? Want some?
What's wrong? Don't you want any?
All right, then. We'll eat it.
lt's awfully good, though
l'm hungry. Aren't you?
For good health and good business...
Mother! Time to eat! Mother?
Buy a couple of pairs of pants for him
on your way home, will you?
- Again?
- Yes. Cheap ones will do
More?
You shouldn't.
Otherwise, your stomach won't get better
Here
Seconds?
This is so nice. lt's so quiet
Don't say a word
How long do you think it'll last?
Say goodbye
Morning. You're early today.
Kozo's still getting ready
Kozo. Kozo!
Morning, lsamu. That's a lovely scarf
- Did you have a fight with Minoru?
- No, l didn't
See you later
What's going on? Very odd...
Such odd children
- What's going on?
- What?
The children from across the way
didn't even say "good morning"
So what?
They both just looked at me
and didn't say a word
Do you think Mrs Hayashi
is still mad at me about yesterday?
- Yesterday?
- About the women's group fees
l don't think so.
Things like that happen all the time
lt's all because ofyour mother's senility,
you know
She didn't say anything to me
lf l hadn't asked her,
she might have spent the money
No, l wouldn't have!
We all forget things
l don't. Not important things
Ofcourse you do!
l should know
What's that?
What have l ever forgotten?
That gas bill l paid for you
ls that all?
You do it, too, you know.
You just ignore your own faults
Enough already, give it a rest!
l'm going out
See you later
Saying she never forgets!
And she didn't even remember
to pay me back
Always shooting her mouth off
How on earth did l get a daughter like her?
Morning
Morning.
Has your husband gone for the day?
Yep
l need a word with you
- What?
- She's an odd one
- The cabaret woman?
- Oh, she's impossible, but l mean Mrs Hayashi
How?
Just because l was late
with the women's group fees...
...she's been telling everyone
l used the money to buy a washing machine
Has she? That's awful
l know. So l went over to complain
She apologised, and l thought
we'd put the matter to rest
But she's obviously still angry.
She's even told her children
When l spoke to them this morning,
they completely ignored me
l can't bear it
ls she really like that?
She is. l was surprised as well
- l never thought she was like that
- l know
She obviously holds grudges,
so you better watch out
You think so? You might be right
Do you think l should return the beer
l borrowed?
- Did you borrow some?
- We were completely out
The other night?
Then you better hurry and return it
You're right. l'm glad you told me
Good morning
- Hello?
- Oh, come in
l forgot all about the beer
l borrowed it the other day
That's all right. There's no rush
And this is for the bus ticket
you bought for me
No, really, it's fine
No, l should return it
Sorry and thank you
Mrs Tomizawa?
Are you there?
Hey, Mrs Okubo's here
Oh, do come in
What is it?
lfyou've ever borrowed something
from Mrs Hayashi, you'd better return it
- Why?
- Apparently, she likes to hold a grudge
No. l've borrowed from her plenty oftimes
But she does. l was told so
l was shocked. She seems well educated,
but one never knows, eh?
You think so?
Our cat stole some of her dried fish.
Do you think l should return it?
Absolutely, you should!
Maybe you're right
l already have.
lt's such a weight off my chest
So, you start with the last letter
ofthe last word
Crow, worm, moon
Okay, what's next?
Yes, Akita
The Moonlight Masked Man
The Moonlight Masked Man?
No, the word has to start with an N
You, Shimizu
lt's Captain Redbreast!
No, no.
Start with the letter N
Yes, Hayashi
What starts with the letter N?
There are lots ofwords that do,
aren't there?
What is it? What's wrong?
What does that mean?
ls something wrong?
The toilet?
What does that mean?
What's wrong?
What is it?
Okay, read it out loud for me
What are you waiting for?
Can't you read it?
You know what it says
Right, stay there
That's all for today
Don't forget to bring
your lunch money tomorrow
- Yes, sir
- Good
And please remember to bring
your lunch money tomorrow
Yes, Miss!
Understand?
Please raise your hand ifyou do
Yes, miss!
What about our lunch money?
Should l tell mum?
- No way. And no more talking
- What do we do, then?
How long do you think
they'll keep it up?
Just ignore them.
They're at that rebellious stage
They take after their father
- What?
- They're so stubborn and awkward
- They take after you, then
- That's so not true. ls it?
lt makes you wonder
What is it?
- What?
- What is it?
- What do you think?
- l don't know. Any ideas, brother?
No
What is it?
A building? A large house?
The government building?
A temple? A hospital?
No?
A school?
School? What about school?
ls it on fire?
Not a fire? lt's not on fire?
Drinking tea? Then what?
Drinking tea and eating?
Money? ls it money?
Got it! The firemen put out the fire,
and you paid them and gave them tea?
- What?
- l wonder...
- Have you got it?
- l haven't got a clue. What's this about?
l wonder...
What could it be?
One, two, three, four, five, six...
He's really good
Ofcourse, my dad works
for the gas company
Minoru's good, too, he's refusing to talk
Not even at school
...five, six, seven, eight
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Hey...why won't you talk?
Don't you find it inconvenient?
Hey, what's wrong?
Did you take a vow or something?
What is it?
Hey
Silly lads
Still eating pumice powder every day?
lfyou keep that up,
you'll die with a stomach full ofstones
- Really?
- Absolutely
You know that seal that died at the zoo?
lts stomach was full ofstones
lt thought the stones that
the visitors threw were food
Who is it?
- Hello
- Oh, it's you. What is it?
What are you doing here, boys?
Why don't you come and watch TV?
Are there any vacant flats here?
l don't think so.
You should ask downstairs
Really?
Do you know of anywhere else?
l don't know. Who's looking?
Me! l want to move.
The neighbours are so interfering
- Don't you know of anywhere at all?
- Not really
You're a cold fish, aren't you? Bye!
Yes?
Oh, it's you
Hello
So you're here?
l have more translation work for you
- Was the other translation all right?
- Yes
l'll be back in four or five days for these
All right. And thanks for the work
Thank you
What happened to these two?
They won't talk
They were scolded for talking too much,
so now they won't talk at all
Really? How funny
What was it you said?
Come on, lsamu. Hey!
- What's the matter with them?
- They said adults talk too much, too
"Good morning. Good evening.
Good day. Have a good day."
Oh, l see. They have a point.
We do say those things
We all certainly do
But such things are perhaps necessary,
don't you think?
lt'd be a dull world
without such conventions
Yes, but the children
don't understand that yet
No, they've no idea about such things
But it makes the world go round
That's what l think, anyway
Hey, lsamu.
What are you angry about?
You're right, l agree
Well, anyway,
let's have another drink
Oh, easy, easy
- Too much?
- No, not at all
Never mind
But drinking and smoking
are a waste oftime, too
But why worry?
You're right
l know how the kids feel
when they pester you to buy a TV
l'd like one, too,
but l can't afford it
Finances aren't the problem.
l'm simply against buying one
l remember hearing someone say that
TVjust produces a society of idiots
ls that so?
What do they mean?
lt means that the Japanese
will be reduced to idiots
Now, that would be a travesty.
l see your point
But what does it really mean?
Hey, mister, what do you think?
- What?
- About television?
Television?
You mean the idiot box?
You've heard that?
Oh, yeah.
TV's a total waste oftime
You think so?
That's what people think, eh?
l guess it's a bad idea to have
too much convenience in life
That's right
A bad idea...
l'm home
Have you come to visit us?
lt's nice to see you.
You're a good boy
Welcome home
Sorry, Mrs Hayashi
ls my wife out?
Thanks so much for house-sitting
Actually, your home's next door
Gosh, sorry about that!
- Do you need a hand?
- No, l'm fine
l'm home
l feel good
Have you been drinking again?
l found the right place this time!
l feel good
What on earth are you on about?
l feel good, so leave me alone
l feel so good
Honey, are you done?
Still in the middle of it
- What time's the truck coming?
- lt'll be here around 3:00, so hurry up
What are you doing? What's the rush?
Looks like the next door neighbours
are moving
l saw. Neighbours can be
a nuisance, though
l feel like moving, too
But wherever you go,
you have neighbours
Unless you live in the mountains, that is
True
Listen, do mice gnaw on pumice stone?
Well...l don't think so
That's odd, then,
because it's disappearing fast
Maybe l should put some rat poison on it
l'm hungry. We haven't had any snacks
l don't think we should eat pumice stone
anymore. Won't we die?
We're not full ofstones yet, are we?
We're okay, right?
Anybody home?
- lt's our teacher
- What'll we do?
Come on
ls that so?
l scolded them for talking too much
l see. At least now l understand
what's going on
The youngest won't talk, either
l'm sorry they've been so much trouble
Raising children is a difficult task
Please be more strict with them at school
- We wouldn't mind at all
- No, l'm afraid l couldn't
Oh, you have a guest?
Please, come in. l was just leaving
Thank you and goodbye
Thank you. l'll make sure they bring
their lunch money tomorrow
Thank you
- Come in, Mr Tomizawa
- Thanks. Excuse me
Beautiful weather, isn't it?
Yes, it's been a lovely spell
- Welcome
- l'm sorry about last night
l was scolded by my wife this morning
You seem in good spirits today
l wanted to tell you my good fortune.
l found a job
Really? That's great
lt's not a big company
Kowa Electric Company. Do you know it?
lt's in Kuromon-cho
- l'm in sales
- That's great
lt's hard work, though
l have to do door-to-door, selling these...
Oh, l see. Toasters, mixers
And washing machines, too
- Yes. How about buying one?
- We couldn't
How about something for you?
Well...
We do monthly instalments as well
We must buy something
to celebrate your newjob
Please do that.
l have plenty ofother catalogues
Just a minute, l'll get them
Back in a jiffy
lt's time for us to think about it, too
What?
Retirement
Want some tea?
Yes, please
Messy, isn't it?
Fun, isn't it?
l want rice
Tastes good
Should've brought some side dishes
- Shall l get some?
- Yes, go get some
Hey, brother...
Hurry up!
Who is it?
- Hello
- Good evening
- Our boys aren't here, are they?
- No. ls anything wrong?
Were they here this afternoon?
No, not today
- What is it?
- The boys ran offsomewhere this afternoon
Really? You must be worried
Yes. But they may be home now.
Good night
Take care
- Goodbye
l wonder what's going on
They're funny, those kids.
Are they still not talking?
l think it's quite interesting
For children, our greetings may seem
mundane, like a waste oftime
l do it all the time at work to sell cars,
l have to
Yes, it acts as a social lubricant
in our world
But important things can be difficult to say
True. Whereas, meaningless things
are easy to say
- You're like that, too
- What do you mean?
- Can't admit you're in love
- What?
l'm talking about Setsuko.
You only talk about the weather and work...
- ...but you never say how you feel
- But that's different
No, it's not. l know
You should get round
to the important things
Why don't you go out and look?
- For what?
- The kids
They've been out since this afternoon?
lt's too long
- Shall l go and have look for them?
- Yes, go on
lt's cold out. Wrap up warm
Check around the cinema, will you?
l'm home. Are Minoru and lsamu back?
- Not yet
- Really?
l went to the teacher's flat, too
What's that?
l got it at the police station
They said they left them and ran away
Where could they have got to?
Do you have any idea?
l'll go and look around
No, l'll go
- Where would they go?
- Nuisances!
lt's cold out. Wrap up warm
- Good evening
- Yes?
Good evening
Hey, come on in
Where have you been?
Dear, they're back
Please don't scold them
They were watching TV
in front ofthe station
Really?
Thank you so much
You silly boys! You made us worry
Well, l must be going
- Thank you so much
- Sorry for the trouble
- Goodbye
Come in
Don't worry. Come on in
Welcome home
Brilliant!
- A TV, right?
- Yeah
- You bought a TV?
- You really bought one, Mum?
- Yes, Father bought you one
- lt's brilliant!
And Mr Tomizawa brought it over
- How much?
- lt's expensive!
- Never you mind
But you two have to study hard now
- Yes, l will!
- l will!
Thanks!
How lucky are we?
Hey, we can watch baseball, too
We are so lucky!
Hey, aren't you two hungry at all?
No. Teacher treated us to noodles
at the station
Dumplings, too!
l see. Not hungry, then?
l'm so happy!
Look here!
lfyou make a racket,
l'll return the TV!
He's lying. His face says so
He's smiling
- l'm off!
Take care
Mum, make sure the TV's all set
when we come home
See you later!
Good morning!
Has Kozo already left?
Kozo. Kozo!
Good morning!
Has Zen gone already?
- Yes, he just left
- Okay
Kozo, hurry up!
- l'm off!
- l'm off, too!
What do you think is going on?
They talked, didn't they, those two?
l wonder what's happened
Listen, Mrs Tomizawa!
What is it?
Hello
- What is it?
- Listen...
Those two Hayashi boys were
so cheerful this morning. Very odd...
Yes. They both said, "Good morning"
Oh, you've got them all wrong
That family is so nice,
and Mrs Hayashi's very understanding
- You think so?
- Yes, you're reading her wrong
l'm going into town. Need anything?
Okay, then
What do you make of her, then?
l guess the Hayashi must've bought
a hot plate or something
You're probably right.
She's a calculating woman
You still eating pumice stone?
lt's bad for you. You'll die
l've stopped and switched to burdock
Nudge me
Now me
Your turn
Rubbish. You're still no good
What's the matter?
l have to go home
l'll come on later
Good morning
- Good morning. Thanks for yesterday
- Not at all
Where to?
- To West Ginza
- Then we can go together
- Lovely day, isn't it?
- lt really is
lt's beautiful
lt looks like this nice weather will continue
Yes
lt does look that way
That cloud's an interesting shape
You're right, it is an interesting shape
lt sort of looks like something
Yes, like something
Such a lovely day
Yes, a really lovely day
You're such a fool
And at your age, too
What a nuisance
Mum, l won't die, will l?
l swallowed pumice stone by mistake
You'd be better offdead,
being absent from school for this
l won't feed you till you're well.
You hear me?
Mum, can l have some clean underwear?
You can go without.
You're not wearing any until you're better
The End