Councilman, when are you going
to be withdrawing from the race?
Councilman!
Councilman, did you know the
murder victim, Rosie Larsen?
No, I did not. Who was driving
the vehicle she was found in?
Rosie Larsen's body was found in the
trunk of a car stolen from this campaign.
The police have asked
me not to comment further.
Does this remind you of what
happened to your wife, Councilman?
This has nothing
to do with that.
A young woman has been
killed... someone's child.
This is not political. It's about us
doing all we can to help the police...
solve a senseless
and brutal crime.
My heart goes out to the
Larsen family for their terrible loss.
Mr. Councilman!
This was some party
they were havin' down here.
Meth, oxy, booze.
Blood's a match to Rosie's type.
Larsen girl a user?
Won't get the tox screen back
for a few days. Didn't seem like it.
But if she was, could
have been an O.D.
Whoever was with her
panicked, dumped her.
I need you to work this thing,
Sarah. Can't do it. You know that.
It's gonna take some delicate
maneuvering. He can't do it.
I'm not staying. Just
till the end of the week.
I got City Hall on my
ass on this thing. You
can't leave this with
him. You know that.
Not my problem anymore.
Well, it is your problem, actually.
You're on the city's dime
till the end of the week.
Look,
clear this thing, and I'm just
an address on a Christmas card.
Principal Meyers.
Oh, my God.
- Hey!
- Councilman!
Damn it! You shouldn't have
listened to the cop. I told you.
That dead girl's gonna
lead the 10:00 news...
and be on the front page
of every paper in the state.
Where is he? You
lying son of a bitch!
Ruth. Why didn't you tell me?
Because the police
asked me not to.
The car was stolen. It
had nothing to do with us.
What, you think they care? This
is what those parasites feed on.
Chappaquiddick? Chandra
Levy? Ring any bells?
We can control
this, Ruth. Shut up!
By the time those whores
are finished with you,
you're gonna be the
punch line of a dirty joke.
- I've had about enough of this.
- Ruth, we can talk this through.
We can get through
this. "We"? "We"?
Oh, no. There's
no we. We are over.
We kept sports equipment
down here years ago.
The kids called it "The Cage."
It hasn't been used in ages.
Who else has keys to
this place? Besides me?
Just our janitor.
Damn.
Front-row seat.
What's his name? The janitor.
Lyndon Johnson Rosales. Why?
Thanks.
I'm hungry. Aunt
Terry's getting Chinese.
I hate Chinese.
Okay. Let's see
what else we got here.
How 'bout tuna fish?
I hate tuna.
Okay.
What do you boys want for
dinner? Chocolate-chip pancakes.
Pancakes are
for breakfast, idiot!
Don't call your brother that.
We can have pancakes.
Chocolate-chip pancakes.
All right. Here we go.
Should we wake up Mom? No,
let Mom sleep. She's tired, Den.
We can make dinner ourselves, right?
You know how to make them, Dad?
It's gotta be on the back of
the box. How hard can it be?
Get me an egg and
some milk, Tom. Okay.
Okay.
Go ahead. Crack that
egg right in there, huh?
All right. Ooh!
Yup. You like crunchy ones, huh?
There you go.
How did Rosie die?
It's okay, Dad.
You don't have to talk about it.
So how long you
staying this time?
You like the L.T.'s pet?
Maybe he just wants
the case cleared.
Maybe I didn't just
find the crime scene.
Assumptions are
your enemy, Detective.
I'm lead on this for
the next few days,
so stop pressing everyone we
question like they're in the box.
Let go of the idea that you
have some B.S. detector.
And how do you know I
don't have one of those?
'Cause you're dressed like Justin
Bieber and eat pork rinds for dinner.
Ooh! Me and your kid
got the same diet, Linden.
Ma'am.
We're with the Seattle P.D.
We're looking for a
Lyndon Johnson Rosales.
No. No here.
We'd like to ask you a few
questions. Can we come in?
Is Lyndon your son?
Does he live here with you? N...
- No Lyndon here.
- No.
He's... He's not here?
'Cause we could... we
could wait. You go, please.
We need to talk to your son.
Lyndon no come.
But we can wait if he's
not here. Lyndon no here.
Mr. Rosales?
Holder, he's here!
- Put your weapon down
right now!
- Lyndon!
Drop your weapon!
Mr. Rosales, we just
want to talk to you.
Lyndon! Lyndon!
Twenty-nine-year-old male
fell from a third-story window.
L.O.C. on arrival.
Depressed skull fracture.
This man's a suspect in a murder
case. When can I talk to him?
After surgery.
Councilman, did you know the
murder victim, Rosie Larsen?
Who was driving the
vehicle she was found in?
Rosie Larsen's body was found in the
trunk of a car stolen from this campaign.
The police have asked
me not to comment further.
Dr. Barnes to C.C.U.
So Rosales likes to show
his junk to teenage girls.
Damn.
And he's got a kid-tiddlin'
record and a couple of 311's.
School missed it.
That's why he ran.
'Cause of his warrants or
because he killed the Larsen girl?
L.B.J.'s alibi'd Friday night.
He got picked up at 9:30. D.U.I.
He spent the weekend
in the drunk tank.
Ouch.
Thanks.
Keep an eye on Rosales for me.
Call me as soon as he's awake.
Yeah.
Hey, babe. Hi.
What are you doing?
Watching M.M.A.
with Leon. That's good.
As long as there's someone
there to keep you warm,
I won't feel so guilty about
staying through the weekend.
- Rick?
-
So much for "I'm gonna be on
the next flight tomorrow," huh?
I'm under a lot of pressure.
Baby, I found the girl. Oakes
wants me to see it through.
Great.
We'll be there Sunday for the
party. I don't care what he does.
Good... because we're
still getting married, right?
Of course.
And when you get married,
there's lots of crap you gotta do,
like the cake, the flowers, the
streamers... crap you said you cared about.
I do care. You know I care.
I'll make this up
to you. I promise.
Just try to get on the plane next
time. I gotta go. Leon's getting jealous.
I love you.
Put on a little more muscle.
Maybe that's the difference.
Hey.
Leftover minestrone
on the stove,
and you don't have to
worry about waking him up.
Five hours of Halo knocked
him on his butt. Thanks, Regi.
How's that quittin'
smokin' goin'? It's fine.
He wanted to wait up, but I told
him he had to go to school tomorrow.
He's not happy.
I could let him smoke
cigarettes all day on the dock,
but I thought school
might be a little better.
That's what you were
doing when you were his age.
A lot more than
that. Yeah, I know.
I want a little more
for Jack than that.
Sonoma will be a
fresh start. He'll love it.
It'll be great. I bet.
So what's holding
you back? Nothing.
Work.
I thought work was over.
So did I.
I gotta get back. I'm just
gonna take a little shower.
Okay. I got clean
towels downstairs.
Thank you for
letting us stay, Regi.
I got my two favorite people in the
whole world for a couple more days.
That's not a bad deal.
Hi. I'm not here right now...
and neither is anyone
else, apparently,
which is weird because
we usually are here.
But not today. Um... I really
don't know where we are.
Uh... Anyway, leave a message,
and I promise that
we will get back to you.
Bye.
Hi. I'm not here right now...
and neither is anyone
else, apparently,
which is weird, because
we usually are here.
But not today. Um... I really
don't know where we are.
Uh... Anyway, leave a message,
and I promise that
we will get back to you.
Bye.
Great seeing you again.
Now, we're having a little
party. I'll phone you about it.
Thank you very much for coming.
If Cicero had bided his
time, he would have gone far.
Instead, the Romans
executed him.
Put his hands and head
on display in the Forum.
You needed to see me, Mayor?
It's unfortunate what happened with
your campaign car and that girl, Darren.
I'd say the race is pretty
much over for you at this point.
But all is not lost. Wait four
years, you'll have my endorsement.
Donors will flee, you lose
this time. No second chances.
So you can get on your knees for
four more years for the developers?
I don't think so. No
need to wallow, Darren.
You didn't really think the police would
keep this thing a secret from me, did you?
Holder, I got the yearbook
from Principal Meyers.
I'm on my way over.
We had a deal. We did.
Then what the hell is
this? It didn't come from us.
Who did it come
from? I don't know.
I played fair with you. I know
you did. I appreciate that.
My campaign is in the gutter
now because I trusted you.
What can I do? Make an arrest.
All right. That was the bell,
people. I need you in your seats now.
♪♪
Oh, damn. Look at her!
Now!
♪♪
People!
Unreal, man.
That's it.
Give me the damn phone. ♪♪
You people never
cease to amaze me.
By now, most of you have
heard what happened to Rosie.
Grief counselors will be, um,
in the gym all day for those...
Sterling. Sterling!
I thought, um, we could
take today's class period...
to talk about it.
I know this may
be a difficult time.
Hey, Sterling!
Sterling, get back here!
I-I don't care what he says.
I'm not gonna do it right now.
You gotta give me some time to
ease in. I mean, she's not stupid.
Uh... Uh, I gotta go,
so I'll call you back.
Thanks. What's up?
Hmm? What? N-Nothin'. Just...
With Rosales. Oh. Oh, yeah.
Um, he's out of surgery.
He's conscious, but he's
all doped up on morphine.
And no visitors.
She's a prison guard.
She's got a crush on me.
So work your magic.
Yo, Mary. Mary, right?
D-Did I tell you about that time
I got pica when I was, like, five?
They had to keep the
Play-Doh locked up around me.
Liked to eat it raw that way.
Mr. Rosales? Can you hear me?
I'm sorry this happened to you.
We know why you ran, but that's
not why I need to talk to you right now.
I know that sometimes you watch
the kids in the basement at school.
That's not my concern.
What I need to know is if
you saw this girl, Rosie Larsen,
in the basement Friday night.
Helping us can help
you, Mr. Rosales.
You saw Rosie
there? You're sure?
Yes.
Who was with her
in the basement?
Was it this guy... Jasper Ames?
You're sure?
- You can't be here.
- Seattle P.D.
I don't know who let you in here,
but you're gonna have to leave now.
This patient is in
critical condition. Uh...
- Look, you two
can't be in here.
- Hey, chill.
Don't tell me to
chill. This is my ward.
He was in the basement
with Rosie? You're positive?
- Yeah.
- Mary!
Yeah? Page Dr. Molnar.
And call Security. Okay.
Hey, relax, girlfriend, all right? We're
leaving. You don't have to do that.
El diablo. What?
El diablo.
I want to assure you that we
are doing everything we can...
to help the police
solve the Larsen case.
But for now, and most
importantly, for the people of Seattle,
I think what we really need
to do is take a deep breath...
and stay the course.
Yeah?
Every one of you in this room...
is helping to change lives with
the work that you do here every day.
So, let's commit to winning
this campaign, shall we?
Nice job.
I spoke with the Register, and Michaud
is willing to give you column space,
but only if it's an
exclusive. Sold.
And I've got some interest in the
All Stars photo op this afternoon.
We're gonna push your
education agenda. Good. Good.
Hey, we stay on message,
and this is gonna blow over.
All these reporters... they
have A.D.D. Yeah, right.
Where you going?
Nice view.
Yeah. I never get tired of it.
What do you have for me?
I checked Jamie and Gwen's accounts.
No e-mails about the Larsen girl.
But I did find this from a few days
ago, leaking Yitanes's endorsement.
Thank you, Nathan.
Yeah.
So Kris Echols is a
meth-dealing skater punk.
He got kicked out of Fort
Washington first week senior year.
His mom reported
him as a runaway. ♪♪
And get this... He's
Jasper Ames's best friend.
So the janitor was the only one
who saw the Echols kid at the dance?
Anyone I.D. Jasper there?
Doesn't make sense. What's
Rosie doing with a dealer?
Well, who you think's gettin'
hooked on crank these days?
Housewives and cheerleaders.
Talk to the parents, see if
they can shed some light.
They've been calling all morning,
pissed off about the Richmond thing.
And you're gonna want to
tell 'em the cause of death, Sar.
- They need to know.
- I can do that... talk to the Larsens.
Uh, no, I'll do it. You
talk to Echols's family.
Okay, boss. ♪♪
Wait a minute. Look at this.
What?
We went over this
yesterday. Look at it again.
Sterling, Rosie and...
That's how Kris got into the dance
without anyone recognizing him.
He wore a mask.
El diablo.
But here we are, folks.
Just days away from the birth of
Seattle's Waterfront Renewal Project!
Groundbreaking on the mayor's
$44.6 million dream project...
takes place tomorrow.
This will allow more
than one billion do...
I'm surprised he didn't throw
in a jab about the Larsen girl.
He didn't have to.
The damage is done.
Yitanes hasn't officially endorsed
him yet. That's good news.
The only thing he has is the
Waterfront, and he knows it.
We stay on message, Darren.
It's a waste of the
taxpayers' dollars.
It's lining his pockets
and the C.D.F.'s coffers.
He's stealing from programs like
yours that really make a difference.
Gwen, spare me the sound bite.
I found our leak...
Who went to the
press about Yitanes.
Why? I don't get it.
He's always been loyal.
This doesn't make sense.
Yeah. Well, there you have it.
He's playing both sides.
Helping Adams, hoping if you
lose, he'll get an appointment.
That's ridiculous.
That's the only thing that makes sense.
You know him. This is just a game to him.
I trusted him.
He doesn't care.
He just wants to win.
What are we gonna do?
Hey. Ready to play some hoops?
We gotta be at the park
at 5:00 for that press thing.
Any luck with the Larsen family?
They're not answering our calls.
All right. Maybe we
can butter 'em up.
Send 'em some
roses. White roses.
No. No flowers.
Flowers die.
She drowned?
Rosie drowned?
I thought you should know.
We had to find out about
that politician in the paper.
I know. I'm sorry. That
shouldn't have happened.
Did he... Is he
the one who did it?
All that we know right now is
that the campaign had a lot of cars.
That particular one was reported
stolen on Saturday morning.
So you haven't
arrested anybody yet?
We are working
on it, Mr. Larsen.
There's a couple of things that have
come up that I need to ask you about.
Did Rosie ever mention
a Kris Echols to you?
He lived down the street.
Him and Rosie used to play
together when they were little. Why?
Did Rosie keep
in touch with him?
No. It was a long time ago.
He and his family moved away from
the neighborhood, like, three years ago.
- He had problems. Drugs, I think.
- What about Rosie?
Did she ever drink or use drugs?
No.
Why are you asking that?
We're throwing a wide net,
looking at everybody your
daughter associated with.
No particular reason.
- He seemed like a good kid.
- Yeah.
Did she suffer?
We think that she was probably
unconscious when the car went in,
so, no.
All right, Aman. You ready
for your final beatdown?
If I thought one was coming.
Yeah! Twenty-one! Oh,
yeah! Nothing but net, D.R.!
We need to wrap
it up, Councilman.
Next time, Aman,
you won't know what hit you.
All right. Glad you guys
got to see this in action.
This All Stars Program is
in 35 parks around the city...
and a key component to Councilman
Richmond's anti-gang initiative.
Is it true Councilwoman Yitanes
has pulled her endorsement...
because of the Larsen murder?
No comments? What about the car?
Any news on who was driving
the car the girl was found in?
Uh, how would we know?
The car was stolen...
Okay. Thanks a lot,
guys. We'll be in touch.
Councilman...
Don't give them any more fodder,
Darren. Let this thing burn itself out.
That won't happen, Jamie.
There's a leak in the campaign.
Yeah. Someone tipped off the
press about Yitanes's endorsement.
And now this?
The cops leaked this. They
never keep their mouths shut.
And Yitanes probably
blabbed herself.
Everybody's playing
both sides now, Darren.
It's the name of the game.
Yeah? Hey, you stay focused.
We got 23 days to
turn this thing around.
We can do it. Hell,
we're gonna do it.
We always have, right?
Kris started using
drugs when he was 13.
First it was pot.
Then... I don't know.
The meth started when
he was in high school.
Where's your son now?
Last time I did try to get him some
help, I found him at Marginal Way.
You know that horrible
place by the bridge?
I don't know what
he did this time,
and I don't want to know.
Maybe you could remember that
he has a mother that loves him...
and who prays
for him every night.
They all do.
Yo, man. Can I get some of that?
Nope.
Man, what a dick.
Got a light?
I'm lookin' for some shards.
I heard Kris is a hookup.
You a cop?
I look like a cop?
Are you a cop?
So what's up? Is he here?
No.
Maybe later.
Can I get some of that?
He ain't here.
Relax, Mom.
It's NarcScent.
Smells like weed, tastes
like weed, it ain't weed.
Used it on busts all the time.
What did Green Hair say?
No Rosie sightings, but she said
Kris is a regular, so he'll be here.
Skate park's walking distance
to the campaign parking lot.
He could've stolen
that car Friday night.
Yeah. Get cozy, Linden.
We gotta wait.
Found a way to lure
Yitanes back to our camp.
Really? Her husband.
The plumber?
Plumbing contractor.
Been a dead weight
on her ass for years.
- Didn't that guy
have his license revoked?
- No, just suspended.
- Paid a little fine. No biggie.
- So?
So, remember the teen
shelters Yitanes is sponsoring?
They're gonna
need toilets, right?
She can't give her
husband the job, but you can.
So I trade my rubber
stamp for her endorsement?
Come on, Darren. Some
plumber's gonna get the job anyway.
Why shouldn't
you benefit from it?
It's interesting how you're so
worried about our chances now.
What are you
talking about? Gwen.
We saw the e-mail, Jamie.
What e-mail?
Okay, this is bullshit.
I never wrote this. Obviously
someone has hacked into my account.
Don't I even get a chance
to defend myself here?
You just did.
I don't believe this.
You're letting sex
cloud your judgment.
- Jamie, enough.
- Screw you.
Screw both of you.
Hey.
I thought I was gonna be back
by dinner, but, um, I'm still working.
You and Regi gonna do takeout?
Great. Don't forget
to tell her thanks.
Hey, Jack, no soda.
You'll be up all night.
Okay.
Chill, Linden.
I mean, I never had dinner
with my mom, and... look at me.
That's comforting.
Kinda young to be out here
alone. How old do you think she is?
Fourteen goin' on
40, like the rest of 'em.
Hey, check it out.
Later, man. What's up, Kris?
♪♪
What the hell, man?
Need to talk to you.
Yeah? I don't need to
talk to you, 5-0. Yeah?
We're taking you in. On what
grounds? I know my rights.
You gonna arrest
me? Didn't think so.
We know you were at Fort
Washington Friday night at the dance.
Whatevs. I'm out. What
did you do to Rosie, Kris?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You gave her some bad shit.
She O.D.'d down in that
hellhole, and then you freaked.
Get off me! Let him go.
I said let him go, Holder.
Your mom says hi!
Dickhead.
Now what?
Let's go.
Why did you tell people I'm
still considering endorsing you?
Because I'm still
hoping you will.
Did I not make
myself clear last night?
You are the kind of liability
I need like a kick in the ass.
Maybe. But I have a proposition.
Sit down, Ruth. No.
I'll be out here if you need me.
You may not need me, but I
understand your husband might.
What are you talking about?
The multimillion-dollar teen
shelter program you've sponsored?
No. No. I don't need
you to make that happen.
No. But you need me to insure that
Yitanes and Sons do all the plumbing.
Wow! How far the
mighty have fallen.
You're surprising
me here, Darren.
I need your sway with the
unions to win this election.
Your husband needs a job.
You must think I'm pretty easy.
Nothing's easy with you, Ruth.
♪♪
What's up, Kris?
They know we were at the
dance, huh? You told them!
I didn't tell them anything! Come
on! What are you talking about?
They know.
I don't get it.
What's his damage with rich boy?
Rosie wouldn't have gone
down in that basement with Kris.
What? She'd go with someone
she trusted, like Jasper.
Let's pick him up. With
what? We've got nothing.
Linden.
Okay. We're on our way.
Teacher found something.
Denny, turn off the TV.
Come help your brother.
Hey. Hi, Mom.
Oh, babe, let me
get that. I'll do that.
No, we got it covered.
Chocolate-chip pancakes, huh?
Yep.
Go on. Take a bath, relax
a little before we eat, okay?
I got it, babe.
Sorry, Dad. I f-forgot.
It's okay, Tom. It's okay.
Hey, why don't you leave it?
Rosie's teacher confiscated a
phone from a student earlier today.
Go ahead, play it.
♪♪ They sent the video to
a bunch of kids at the school.
Gettin' off on this?
Bitch, you like this,
don't you, Rosie? No!
Well, I do. ♪♪
Here I come.
Stop moving.
That slut. Yeah.
They did it together.
Bring 'em in.
The next mayor of our
fine city, Mayor Richmond!
Well, thank you.
English - US - Line 21