Previously on AMC's
The Killing...
Rosie Larsens' body was
found in the trunk of
a car stolen
from this campaign.
By now most of you have
heard what happened to Rosie.
Grief counselors will be...
Sterling!
I did find this from
a few days ago.
Leaking Yitanes' endorsement.
Don't I even get a chance
to defend myself here?
You just did.
Screw both of you.
He was in the
basement with Rosie?
Rosie's teacher
confiscated a phone
from a student earlier today.
They did it together.
Let me out of here, you bitch!
Let me out!
Let...Me...Out!
You can't keep me in here.
I know my rights.
I didn't do anything to her!
What do you want, huh?
What?
I didn't kill her, I swear.
So, Rosie, senior year.
Where you gonna be
10 years from now?
Uh...Well, I mean,
who knows what's gonna happen?
Uh, today is all that matters,
and, uh, I want...
I don't know...
um...I want to
see everything,
see the world.
Uh...
I am just so ready
to start living, I guess.
Was that okay?
Tell her that.
What?
Tell her you didn't kill her.
Look at her.
Tell her.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
This kid's been here all night.
He's jonesing...
Ready to break.
You think?
Ames is in the waiting room
with his lawyer.
You're not gonna get much.
It helps put
the pressure on kris
knowing his friend
might want to cut a deal.
You talking to him?
Yeah. Holder will take
the tweaker.
Is it okay
if I use your office?
Ah. That junkie in there
looks better than you do.
Why don't you clean yourself up
and put on a suit?
Hey, your date's with me.
We thought you'd be more
comfortable with your father here,
but it seems he wasn't
able to make it.
Mr. ames is currently
out of the country.
This is just a courtesy visit
on our end.
You can direct any questions
you have to me.
A video has come
into our possession
taken the night
of Rosie Larsen's murder.
She's in it.
So's your client.
What video?
Mr. ames, please.
Would you like to see it?
As you can see, we have a wide
selection to choose from.
This lovely two-toned
brushed-steel model
boasts a white velvet interior
in a French fold design,
eternal rest adjustable bed,
and matching pillow and throw.
And all our caskets fit the
standard 30-inch burial vaults.
Burial vaults?
Protection for your loved one
against the outside
weather elements...
rain and so forth.
The list price for these
models begins at $2,000.
Of course,
there's always cremation...
considerably less expensive...
no.
I understand.
Then you'll want to consider
a flower spray for the casket
or perhaps wreaths
for the church.
That's a beautiful choice
for a young girl.
The list price is $3,800.
We have reasonable
payment plans,
if that's your concern.
No, we're set.
Then I'll just need a nice dress
for your daughter.
You would like her
in a nice dress, wouldn't you?
I wish I had good news,
but I don't.
You're dropping fast
across the board,
losing traction with your
key constituencies, even.
Mayor's now got
an 8-point lead,
so, frankly, you're screwed.
The Yitanes endorsement
didn't stop the hemorrhaging?
No, Adams is choking
the airwaves,
hammering you
with that dead girl.
But the car was stolen.
We had nothing to do with it.
Well, clearly, that message
isn't getting through.
What you need is a media
blitz... ads, billboards.
Yeah, we need to remind voters
that you're the anti-crime guy
and that Adams never
gave a damn till now.
Better hurry before he grabs up
the airtime that's left.
Well, then let's do it
right now.
With what money?
Thank you, Michael.
We need to go to Tom Drexler.
No.
He hates Adams.
He hates politicians.
He thinks we're all hand puppets
for rich lunatics like him.
I don't know.
Maybe we are.
Darren, he could be
a good friend to us.
How?
I'm not making a deal
with a guy whose patron Saint
is Ayn Rand.
You won't have to. All he
cares about is screwing Adams.
We help with that,
we're golden.
At least talk to him.
We need someone with
that kind of money right now.
One thing Jamie was right about
was using him.
Get me my donors list.
I'll start making phone calls
after the committee meeting.
Let me at that bitch.
Give her to me.
It's not what you think.
Looks pretty clear to me.
We didn't do anything
to her, okay?
My client doesn't need to
answer any of your questions.
You don't seem like the type
that shares your toys.
And that's what Rosie was,
right? A toy?
This is over.
Let's go, Mr. ames.
Wait, wait, I can explain.
It's in your best interest
not to... just shut up!
It... it isn't
what you think.
Just turned 18.
Ain't gonna be no comfy
juvie digs for you.
You're gonna be wearing
a micro mini mini
by the time you get out
of adult pen.
Jasper gets the hot chick,
and I get you?
Yeah.
They know you got the itch
like me?
Damn.
Boyfriend laid it on you.
Jasper's crazy, okay?
He hated Rosie.
Yeah, you're just his wingman,
right? Along for the ride?
She always said hi.
Rosie didn't treat me
like I was...
A rock-bottom junkie?
What you gonna tell me next?
You used to walk home together
from school?
You got a minute? I'm in the
middle of something here, linden.
I know.
Let's go.
Yo, I'll check you later,
all right?
Fine.
Another movie?
I want popcorn.
Hey, you shut up, all right?!
Yeah.
Let me at that bitch.
Give her to me.
That's what you got?
Man, you don't know shit.
Hey, mayor.
Jimmy.
Say hello to your dad for me.
Yes, sir.
- Hey, Al.
- Hey.
Give me the usual.
You got it.
And get him another of whatever
the hell he's drinking.
Interesting choice
in venue, mayor.
This place and me go way back.
Used to wait
for my old man outside.
Blackout drunk.
Me, 9 years old, dragging
his sorry a... back home.
Spent a lot of hours
looking at that, wanting more.
I heard the story, mayor.
I just don't understand
why Seattle needs
another yuppie mall.
Not exactly a boon
for the everyman.
Screw the everyman.
I'm the everyman.
And that thing's gonna
bear my name, be my legacy.
Not bad for a poor kid
from highland park.
I hear you're
from pigeon point.
White trash...
Just like you.
Waterfront
revitalization program.
A vote for Adams
is a vote for experience.
Lesley Adams,
a name you can trust.
Look at that, hmm?
This message paid for by...
Can't say I was too surprised.
Your situation with Richmond.
Guy's an amateur,
not ready for the big leagues.
How do you figure?
Carpetbagging rich kid who
saved some souls a few years.
He doesn't know how to win
'cause he never had to.
I believed in that guy.
I guess it was
a one-way street.
Maybe you're right.
I know I'm right.
That's why I asked you here.
So, how about it?
How about what?
Come over and be part
of a winning team for once.
Mrs. Danzinger,
you've been a generous donor,
and I really hope I can
rely on your support again.
I'm sorry, councilman.
We're not going to be able
to help.
No, I...
Not at this time.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Of course.
Thank you for your time.
Senator Eaton's office.
Hi. It's Gwen.
Hi, Gwen.
I need to see the senator.
Does he have an opening?
Let me check.
You and Rosie
were best friends.
Yeah. I guess.
You guess?
I mean...We are.
Were.
Rosie's dead.
I know.
So, why'd you go down
to the cage with her boyfriend?
Did they force you?
No!
There was a lot of blood down there.
I get really bad nosebleeds.
I've gone to the hospital
for them.
But they didn't make me.
I mean, I was drunk,
and Jasper thought it'd be funny
if I put on her witch costume.
So what?
Rosie was okay with that?
She'd already left, didn't
tell me where she was going.
She never even said goodbye.
Mm.
You were mad at Rosie.
She changed so much, you know?
After she broke up with Jasper.
She'd never hang out,
disappear during fourth period,
tell her mom she was spending
the night, and she wasn't.
Where was she going?
I don't know.
I saw her get on the bus
a bunch of times.
Which bus?
Outside of school...
the 108.
What do
you think she was doing?
I think she met someone...
Someone she couldn't
tell anyone about.
Not even her bff?
We wasted a lot time
'cause of you, Sterling.
Why'd you lie?
I-I don't know.
Why'd you go down there
with him?
'Cause he was nice to me, okay?
No one is nice to me.
I mean, not like they are
to Rosie.
I'm like...
Not even there
when she's around.
I didn't mean to hurt her.
I didn't, but...
Don't you ever just
want to feel like...
You're here?
If Rosie was having an affair,
it might explain the shoes.
That key didn't fit
her school locker, right?
No.
M-maybe she had some
secret lockbox or something
where she stashed the guy's
love letters and stuff.
Where? We already
checked her bedroom.
I'll talk to the Larsens...
I'll do it. I'm meeting them
at the station.
'Course you are.
I-I love this partnership.
Y-you do
whatever you want,
and I spend my time
chasing you down.
Is there a problem?
Rosie was sneaking out
during school,
taking the bus,
maybe meeting someone.
Yeah? So?
The 108 doesn't hit
her neighborhood from here,
from fort Washington.
Find out where she went.
Sorry to hear
about the dead girl.
We have it under control.
I've been at this a lot longer
than you have, Gwyneth.
Maybe it's time to admit
you bet on the wrong horse.
I appreciate the concern,
but I know what I'm doing.
Tom Drexler.
Can you get me a meeting?
Well, it depends.
Is this you asking...Or Darren?
He doesn't know I'm here.
Interesting.
Going behind his back.
Maybe you have a bit more
initiative than I thought.
I told you, dad.
I'm doing this my way.
Your way?
Is that what you call
sleeping with your candidate?
Yeah?
The coroner can facilitate
the transfer
to the funeral home.
You'll just need to tell them
where to send her.
There's something that I need
you to look at before you go.
Um...Do you recognize
these items?
Are they Rosie's?
We think so, yes.
Did Rosie have
a lockbox at home?
I don't think so.
We think she may have been
seeing someone.
I told you,
she broke up with Jasper.
Not Jasper.
Possibly an adult.
No, my daughter's
not like that.
Y-you don't know her.
Y-you don't... you don't know
anything about her.
Excuse me.
Hi, Regi.
Sure, I can pick up Jack.
He's at the boat?
Sorry about that.
I'm so sorry,
Mrs. Larsen, Mr. Larsen.
Are we done here?
I'm sorry.
This is
my one-on-one?
Well, let's make the best
of the opportunity we have.
That means smile, Darren.
I'm not sure that'll happen.
At least you both
like basketball.
About 3:00 in the morning,
we come back,
and we find him in the hallway
completely naked...
Welcome to the snake pit.
I didn't think this was
your kind of scene, Darren.
I could say the same
about you, mayor.
Oh, I just dropped by
to toast the king of Seattle...
And stick my waterfront project
up his a... while I was at it.
Well, you do know how
to come bearing gifts.
It's nice you two are a pair.
In this racket,
it's a miracle to find someone
you can really trust, hmm?
Ladies and gentlemen!
Look who we have here.
It's our very own
mayoral candidates.
In this corner, mayor Adams.
Don't let that baboon smile
fool you.
No doubt,
he will steal your money
and then stab you in the balls.
And here we have our challenger,
Darren Richmond...
bright-eyed, bushy-tailed,
"yes, we can!"
I got an idea.
Screw the election.
How about the two of you
finish it right here,
mano a mano?
What say you?
Winner take all?
Much as I'm sure the mayor
would love to show off
his full-court game...
I think I'll take my chances
with the voters.
Darren Richmond.
No, I'm telling you, linden,
this is stupid.
Did you ask if he had seen her?
No, the driver
couldn't I.D. Her.
I need you to check again.
Yeah, whatever.
Yo, chief, take one last look?
You seen this girl?
No.
Jack? I'm here.
Let's go.
Aah!
Gotcha, Lucy.
Just a matter of time.
Rick!
You scared the crap out of me.
Look, you couldn't
make the tasting...
I brought the tasting to you.
Regi was in on this?
Yes.
Was Jack, too?
Yes, everybody lied to you.
Uh, it's called a surprise.
The normal human response
is shock, laughter,
jumping up and down, or you could
launch an investigation...
Okay, I get it. ...
Or establish a timeline.
Shut up.
I was a jerk
last night. Sorry.
No, I was... am.
I brought you and Jack
some clothes.
Oh, you rock.
What's this?
Nothing.
It's just a scratch.
It's not happening again.
Is it?
What?
Chasing after a dead girl.
No, it's not.
New partner complaining again.
He can wait.
New partner.
I mean, the new guy.
Rick, come on.
I can't compete with a ghost.
I mean, I can, right?
But I won't.
You don't have to.
What time are Jack and regi
coming back?
I sent them
to a French gangster film.
It's like five hours long.
Jack should be
falling asleep...
Right about now.
You really
thought this through.
Are you gonna
put that gun away?
Maybe.
The service
will be about your daughter...
The way she was meant
to be remembered.
We appreciate that, father.
Have you thought about hymns?
There are some very nice
selections in here.
Maybe you could pick out a few
you'd like to consider.
Yeah, yeah, I'll take a look.
Mitch.
You got any hymns
you want to hear?
We'll go with the usual, then.
I think I have
everything I need.
Your daughter is with God now,
Mrs. Larsen.
He's watching over her...
over all of you.
He always is.
What good is that to me?
She's not supposed to
be with God.
She's supposed to be with me.
Mitch, come on.
My daughter...
she was out there alone.
And she was scared and she
was hurt and she was alone.
Tell me.
Tell me, where was God then?
Look at this shit hole
of a waterfront.
You know, there should be
a stadium there.
My stadium.
Could you imagine hearing the
roar of the crowd from up here?
Gives me a hard-on
just thinking about it.
Another vanity project
like the mayor's.
Afraid I can't help you.
Why are you here?
'Cause Adams has been
robbing this city blind
for almost a decade.
It is time for a change.
Oh, man.
How does a rich kid
from Connecticut
get right here, right now,
talking mumbo jumbo
about the underprivileged?
25 years ago,
I took a ride on a bus.
I just never got off.
I get it.
You got to stay in character.
I can respect that.
You know...Most politicians
are so in love
with the sound
of their own garbage,
they can't keep
their mouth shut.
I like you, Richmond.
As I said,
I'm not here to help you.
Well, maybe one day you will.
But for now, I want Adams
to go to his grave
pissing in his adult diaper,
knowing he lost this thing
because of me.
That alone will be worth it.
Stan!
What are we doing here?
Gonna have to sell it.
You bought this?
Serious?
Does Mitch know?
Supposed to be a surprise.
Rosie never had a backyard.
You want to do something
about that guy, that Richmond?
Just say the word.
We'll take care of it.
Like old times.
I don't do that anymore.
Hey, girl.
How about you and I take a trip
down to the cage...
Have some fun...
Maybe squeeze
a nosebleed or two in?
Screw you, dickhead!
Remember, Sterling...
"no" means "yes."
Hi.
I'm so sorry,
Mrs. Larsen.
You have nothing
to be sorry about.
When you saw her on Friday,
how was she?
She looked...Happy.
Was she seeing anybody?
Anybody that she didn't
want us to know about?
I... I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I have to go,
Mrs. Larsen.
Okay.
I'll see you?
Yeah. Bye.
Janek.
Witam mój stary znajomy.
I heard about Rosie.
My condolences.
I bought a house
before all this.
I can't move my wife,
my kids now.
I'm paying rent.
I got a mortgage.
I got funeral expenses.
For 17 years, you ignored me...
Walked right past me
on the street.
You know why.
Forget it.
Wait.
Family always comes first.
We were never family.
My best to Mitch.
Hey, Al.
It's all yours.
Hey, humor me, man.
Have you ever seen this girl
on the bus?
Yeah, I recognize her.
Seen her a few times.
You sure about that?
Look around, son.
Ain't a lot of white girls
on the end of this journey.
You remember where she went?
End of the line.
Mrs. Larsen?
Sorry, I don't, uh...
I don't mean to intrude.
You mind?
No. No.
I'm Bennet.
Rosie was a great kid.
Kids like her are, uh...
Why I got into teaching
in the first place.
She was so smart
and, uh... and eager to learn.
Rosie wanted, uh...
She wanted the world, you know?
Mr. Larsen?
The front door was open.
I hate to disturb you,
but I need to check
Rosie's room again
to make sure
we didn't miss anything.
I'm sorry about what happened
at the station.
You said she didn't suffer.
You should've told us.
Rosie loved poetry, literature.
Rosie wrote her semester paper
on this author.
This was her favorite book.
Sarah?
She's not here.
Get used to it.
So, you thought you'd help
yourself to our wedding cake?
Well, it was here.
Think we can do it?
Do what?
Eat it all.
That's right.
Come on.
I can't do this solo.
Yeah.
Chocolate raspberry filling.
Mmm.
How's the white ganache?
It's okay.
Yeah?
Mmm.
Feeling it?
Feeling what?
The sugar rush.
Kind of. Whatever.
I'm in.
Adams admit
to planting the leak yet?
Not yet.
Give me some time.
You know where to find me.
Hey.
How'd you know it wasn't me?
Because if you wanted
to screw me,
you'd have found
a smarter way to do it.
Excuse me, gentlemen,
detective holden
from Seattle PD
I'm looking for this girl.
Have you seen her around?
Yeah, I've seen her.
She come here
with that guy over there...
In the photo.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com