♪♪
Friday. It was... It was...
Friday before
Rosie left for school.
She was in the garage
getting her bike and...
Did she seem
different in any way?
Did she say anything to you,
Mr. Larsen, before she left?
I was on the phone
taking an order. She...
She just waved.
And that was the last time
you saw your daughter?
Anyone you can think of
that might have done this?
Mrs. Larsen?
Her fingernails.
What-What was that?
They were broken.
Why?
Was your daughter
involved in politics?
No, no. She's-She's quiet.
She'd... stay at home most weekends.
Hangs out with her brothers and...
sometimes her friend Sterling.
What about this
boyfriend, Jasper?
Lasted only a few
weeks. Rosie broke it off.
I think in the summer.
He ever hurt your
daughter, Mr. Larsen?
I should have got off the phone.
I should have said good-bye.
Well, these were
found on the body.
Keys, jewelry.
Coroner's got no cause of death yet.
You having a talk with the campaign?
Yeah, I'm about to call them.
No, you do it.
Political nature of this case,
deputy com's gonna be watching.
So you have to dot
your i's on this one.
I handed in my paperwork.
I don't work here anymore.
Paperwork's sitting
on my desk till I sign off.
- You found her, Sarah.
- And I have a wedding to plan.
Yeah, it's in what? Three weeks.
Give me 24 hours,
then you can go.
Sir, you know I
used to work point...
on Undercover busts
down at County, right?
Rick, hold on a second.
Oh, and, uh, car keys
were found in the ignition.
Could be somebody inside
the campaign. Keep me posted.
Did you get my message?
Yeah. Uh, where's Jack?
With Regi on the
boat. He's fine.
Okay, good. Oakes
is making me stay.
You're kidding me.
Just till tomorrow.
Rick, I'm so sorry.
This is crazy. Okay.
Well, cancel the
wedding. It's over.
Might as well tell you. I'm
in love with another woman.
Strawberry blonde. Hot.
She has the softest,
smoothest, "rubberiest" skin.
And the best thing
about her? She's here.
Oh, and she's naked.
Candy Cane's a lucky girl. Yeah.
Hey, get home to me soon.
I will. I love you. Bye.
I appreciate you keeping
this just to family for now.
The first 48 hours
are the most important.
When can we bring Rosie home?
Um, soon.
We'll have a unit over at your house
later to go through your daughter's room.
Why'd you want to know
if she was into politics?
We're looking at every angle.
You should get
home. Get some rest.
I'm sorry for your loss,
Mrs. Larsen, Mr. Larsen.
Will you find who did this?
We'll do our best.
Yeah.
We took in close to 24K tonight.
The blue hairs of Seattle
were sufficiently charmed.
You must be exhausted.
Nope.
Well, good, because I have
a nice pinot waiting for us.
Hello. Yes, this is she.
I don't... I don't understand.
Yes. We'll meet
you at the office.
That was the police.
That missing girl
from the high school...
They found her body, Darren,
in one of our campaign cars.
We'll need to know who
had access to your vehicles.
Absolutely. This is terrible.
I don't understand how our campaign
can have anything to do with this.
Where were you this weekend?
Uh, Tacoma, Friday night,
then back here in the city,
attending several campaign events.
I can get you a list. We were both
with the councilman around the clock.
Was Rosie Larsen connected
to the campaign in any way?
No. I've checked everything,
including our volunteer lists.
So Friday, you were campaigning
out of town, Councilman?
Uh, I was taking a much-needed
break. I can provide the number of the inn.
The owner will
confirm I was there.
And the owner was with you
around the clock too, huh?
Why don't you start looking
through those personnel records?
I'm sure it's a long list.
I put our staff files
on a flash drive.
I'll have to send the records
from the campaign office.
Is there anyone else who
can vouch for you Friday night?
I can. I was with
the councilman.
We'll need a statement
from both of you.
- Not until
we issue a press release.
- I'd rather not go public now.
It's not up to you. We're in
the middle of a campaign.
Whoever did this hid her well.
Our only advantage is he
doesn't know we found her.
How much time do you need?
Till midnight at least.
I'll be in touch.
Councilman.
Oh, screw that. There is
no way we are sitting on this.
Darren, you're not seriously considering
it, are you? What do you recommend I do?
Call a press conference immediately
and express outrage at this tragedy.
You gotta go on the attack.
Adams has had his head so far
up Columbia Domain Fund's ass...
that crime has skyrocketed 12%.
In fact, if it wasn't for him, dead
girl would probably be alive today.
How do you do that
with a straight face?
We're a month away from the
election. This thing will sink us.
Not if we play it right.
Court the girl's family.
Speak at her memorial.
And say what exactly?
That you know what they're going
through because you've been there yourself.
No.
We send out a press release by
noon. Your private investigator, Penato?
Have him start vetting our people, and find
out what the hell happened with that car.
Darren, he's right you know.
Try to look at this
as an opportunity to
tell the voters once
and for all about Lily.
I am not using my wife.
What are we going
to do about Yitanes?
She'll withdraw her
endorsement tonight if we
blindside her with this,
and you need the unions.
Set up a meeting for
noon. I'll tell her then.
A reporter from the
Record called yesterday.
He was tipped off about Yitanes.
Someone sent an e-mail from the office.
Who?
He wouldn't say.
I want you to check everyone's
accounts here at the campaign. Be discreet.
Yeah, I'll get Nathan
on that right away.
How old was she? The girl?
Uh, I don't know.
We're gonna take the later flight,
Jack. You can start school tomorrow.
No, I'll pick you
up in a few hours.
Yeah, you can go on the
water with Regi in the morning,
but don't forget to
wear your life vest.
Uh, I-I really... I really
appreciate the help.
You're welcome. Thanks a lot.
The campaign car was
reported stolen Saturday
morning by a couple
of campaign workers.
This is the police
report. Who drove it last?
Some female volunteer
last Wednesday.
It's been on the
lot till it got jacked.
What were the keys
doing in the ignition?
These dumb asses
keep them there.
Says it makes it easier for
their people to drive them off.
So where to next, boss?
Are you still mad about that,
what I said to the Larsens?
I mean, I can handle 'em.
You know, the guy probably punched
Rosie in the face before he grabbed her.
That's what they do to kids.
That's why the head wounds.
You want to tell that to
the parents, go ahead.
You want me to get
you something to eat?
No.
Jesus, how could this happen? How
could she be missing all weekend?
I just don't get it.
Hey.
I didn't tell the boys nothin'.
But Tommy's so scared,
you know? Asking questions.
I just don't know what
to say to him, Stan.
I could pick 'em up from school.
They should be here with you,
right? You want me to go get 'em?
We'll do it. We gotta keep
things normal for them.
Yeah.
You didn't sleep, babe.
You should get some sleep.
Yeah.
♪♪
What are you doing? That's
supposed to be on the truck already.
Oh, come on. Come on,
guys. You're killing me here.
Jonesy. Jonesy, you gotta be
in Greenwood for that pick-up.
I told you like two hours
ago, man. I know. I'm on it.
Stan. You hear
anything about Rosie?
Let's fold this up and get
out of here. Yeah, we're goin'.
Hey, we ain't paying
you to stand around.
Get outta here already.
You too. Both of you.
Got it. I heard you.
Cops called. They said me and
the guys gotta go to the station?
What's goin' on?
Stan?
Hey, what's your
problem, Sterling, huh?
Telling Rosie's dad she was
at my house? What the hell?
Then where is she? Get off...
Yeah, like I'd know.
I'm not sticking
it to her anymore.
Jasper!
What?
The police are here.
Rosie's missing. They
want to talk to you.
You too, Sterling. Come on.
I drove Rosie to the dance,
and we, like, hung out.
But then I couldn't
find her, so I left.
I thought... I mean, she
was gone all weekend,
so I thought maybe
she went to Jasper's.
She would do that, you know.
Go to his house.
She didn't go there.
I don't know where
she went. I'm sorry.
So Jasper, he
wasn't at the dance?
I already told you he
wasn't. I'm not lying.
I didn't say you were lying.
We have a video of the dance.
It's a yearbook thing. I can
get that for you if that'll help.
Hey, it's not your fault,
Rosie disappearing.
I know.
Picked up some
old lady Friday night.
Some bar in Tukwila.
I think Lee Ann,
Anna Lee, that...
What, do you want to call her?
Hey, you can't do that.
What's the name of the bar?
The Blue Moon.
And what time did
you meet this woman?
Uh, 8:00, 9:00,
10:00. I don't know.
Look, she was on her
fourth Miller High Life.
Told her I had a
six-pack at home.
You know how to charm 'em.
Well, it doesn't take
much. Ones your age.
How long did you
and Rosie go out?
We didn't. Look, we hooked
up for like two seconds.
And then she got bored with you?
- What the hell's going on here?
- Mr. Ames. Your secretary said
you weren't available.
This is over. Now.
Your son's not under arrest.
I was just talking to him.
You want to talk to him?
You contact my attorney.
Uh, my phone.
She insisted on
speaking with Jasper.
I want to be alone with my son.
Dad, I can explain...
What did you do this time?
- Come on. We're rolling.
- Look scary. ♪♪
Come on, Rosie.
So nobody I.D.'d the
campaign car at the school.
- Doesn't mean it wasn't there.
- I don't know.
I'm feeling the
boyfriend for the perp.
What's Jasper doing
driving Richmond's car?
That kid's a douche.
Sorry, little man. I don't care.
Well, I do. Got anything
in the school locker?
Yeah. Books,
notebooks, algebra books.
- I hate algebra.
- Me too.
Yeah? So, like, check this.
A biker goes blah-blah
distance at eight miles per hour...
and then the same fool, he
bikes back at 10 miles per hour.
So what's the average
round-trip rate?
I don't know.
And I don't give a shit. Holder.
Cell calls to home,
parents' phones, Sterling.
Not much of a social life.
Till that boyfriend.
What was she doing with him?
Good girl with no secrets.
She lied to her mom
about her costume.
And her Fabrizio Bianchis.
There's no way she could afford
these. You're lookin' at two G's easy.
How do you even know
that? How do you not?
- Mom shops at Ross, that's why.
- Ohh!
Maybe you should go get
some chips or something.
Jasper could have bought
these. Tryin' to win her back.
No candy bars. Something
healthy like corn chips.
Yeah, Funyuns,
son. Get your fiber.
I mean, that could work out.
Like raising your kid
on vending machines.
Ha, ha, ha.
Don't feel bad, Linden. I mean,
you-you really ain't that bad.
So little man and your
boyfriend, they get along?
My fiancé. Yep, they do.
That's good 'cause
my mom's boyfriends?
Whoo! They had it out for
me. They were like lions.
Like kill the cub to get the
female back in heat. It was like...
Jasper Ames.
Boyfriend. Arrested
back in April for auto theft.
Took a neighbor's
Maserati out for a joyride.
Guy never pressed charges.
Dad owns half of Mercer Island's
waterfront. It's not surprising.
- So how we doing with Richmond?
- Alibi checked out.
Staff records too. None of
'em got kid-tiddling records.
And Larsen's employees cleared.
So, that makes
Jasper our best bet.
Hmm.
You ready for the bad news?
Richmond's issuing a
press release in an hour.
Nathan checked all campaign
and office e-mails. Nothing.
Have him look again.
Any word on the investigation?
Penato said the cops
have been at the school
all morning. Looks like
they're focusing there.
Are they close to an
arrest? He couldn't tell.
He also checked our staff against
county criminal records and ViCAP.
We're in the clear.
Oh, that's good news.
Oh, it gets better.
The campaign car? Reported
stolen Saturday morning.
Lot of thefts in that
lot the last two months.
- Crap security.
- Lucky for us.
So our connection to
this is purely coincidental.
Psst, psst, psst. What are
you all whispering about?
Ruth. I was wondering when
you'd make your grand entrance.
And I'm dying to know the big,
bad secret you're gonna tell me.
Can I get you anything? Uh, cinnamon
latte, double pump, soy. Make it fast.
Sure thing, Ruth.
I'm really looking
forward to this evening.
The unions have always
been important to me.
Then lose the suit. Longshoremen
and machinists don't take to Armani.
That's what I love about you.
You cut right through the bullshit.
So I will too. Hold on.
- Something's come up.
- I'm sorry to interrupt.
If I could just steal
you for a moment.
You can't issue that press release.
Maybe I didn't make myself clear.
Yes, you did. Now if you don't
mind, I'm in the middle of a meeting.
Hold off and I'll tell the press
how cooperative you were.
How you put this family's tragedy
ahead of your own campaign.
And if I don't?
You will be the candidate who
obstructed a child's murder investigation.
You have until midnight,
and then we go public.
Excuse me.
Darren... Holder? What is it?
What are you doing? At the
school? Okay. I'll be there.
You can contact
me at this number.
Detective Holder will take
over the case tomorrow.
Thank you for your help.
You didn't give me
much choice, did you?
And, Councilman, you might want
to call off your dog at the school.
He won't find anything.
How did you know about him?
I was guessing.
And I just confirmed it.
Thanks for your time.
What are you doing?
Call that reporter you
know, Max Michaud.
Tell him he has an
exclusive, but embargoed
until after Yitanes's
announcement tonight.
Candidate shows character
in face of crisis. Not bad.
We make the cop happy.
We control the story.
I'll meet him after the
announcement tonight.
What do we do about her?
Now this may come out in
the next few hours or days.
I just wanted to
keep you in the loop.
I'm hoping it won't,
but you just never know.
Okay. For God sakes,
Darren, what is it?
I smoked pot in college.
It was stupid, I know,
but I inhaled, Ruth.
Are you stoned now? What?
No. Are you?
Just don't get caught with
some intern's face in your crotch.
You'll be the next mayor.
God.
That's all you
needed to tell me?
Scout's honor.
Dad! Why are you here with Mom?
What's wrong, Mom?
Come here, baby. Let's
get that hat on you. It's cold.
- Let's go home, boys.
- But I want to fly my kite.
Not now, baby. Maybe
a little bit later, okay?
Yeah? Hey, it's Belko.
There's a bunch of cops here.
Said they had to look at Rosie's room.
Maybe the boys
shouldn't see this, right?
Yeah, let me know when
they're done. You got it.
You did so good.
Cops are at the house.
Hey, we got a little time.
Let's go fly that kite, huh?
All right!
Come on, baby. Let's go.
Come on, Tommy.
What do ya got?
I got a fish filet and
a veggie burger but...
What did you call me
down here for, Holder?
Okay.
Detective. Here you go.
Found it in a Dumpster.
Rosie's wig. From the dance.
I'm Detective Linden. This is
my partner, Detective Holder.
Can I get a show of hands if
you saw Rosie at the dance.
Rosie was wearing a
witch costume, pink wig.
Maybe one of you
saw her after the dance,
on her way home
or getting into a car.
None of you saw her?
Should I bring in
the next group?
Yeah.
You let me know, Mrs. Parsons, if
that disability check doesn't show up.
I know you've been
waiting over a month for it.
I will, Mr. Richmond. You
know you've got my vote.
Thank you. Take care
of yourself now, all right?
Thank you, Mr. Richmond. Thanks.
You know, Yitanes is going
to eat you alive if she finds out.
Jamie, she will already have publicly
given me her endorsement. No going back.
Unless she finds out before
tonight. Plenty of time to tell her.
She looks frail, Mrs.
Parsons, but she's not.
Took care of her husband, Joe, for
a year after he lost his legs in Iraq.
Brought him out to the
back porch, bathed him.
Joe was a big guy. Wow.
Now she has to fight just
to get her disability check.
That's why we're here.
I'm done talking about Yitanes.
Vern.
- How are you?
- Doing fine, Councilman.
Oh, it's good to see
you. Good to see you too.
Okay, Belko. Call me when they're
done, all right? Yep. Not a problem.
Mom... where's Rosie?
Denny.
Come on. Let's go over
to your mom and Tommy.
But I want to fly my kite.
I know, I know. Come on.
Hey, guys, uh, me and your ma...
we... we have something
to tell you about your sister.
What, Dad?
You remember when Nana was sick,
and we went to visit her in the hospital?
Grandma said she didn't like
the hospital 'cause it smelled bad.
Yeah.
And... And then one day...
she wasn't there anymore.
And we couldn't visit her.
You remember where
I told you she went?
You said Grandma went to heaven.
That's...
That's where Rosie
is now, in heaven.
When's she coming back? When you
go there, you don't come back, dummy!
I'm not a dummy!
She's not coming
back 'cause she's dead!
Tommy, come here.
Come here.
Let me go! Get off
of me! Get off of me!
Tommy! Here, baby. Baby,
come here. Come here.
Shh.
We're gonna be ok...
We're gonna be okay.
Right, Son?
Thanks for meeting
me, Nathan. Yeah.
Gwen tells me you, uh, had
all the e-mail accounts checked.
Nothing was sent to the Record
yesterday. I checked twice.
How about Gwen? Jamie?
You check their accounts?
Um, I-I didn't, no.
Well, do it.
Then report back to me. Clear?
Yeah.
Ready? I gotta pick up Jack.
I think I'm gonna stay for
a while. Do some digging.
Into what? We got
nothing from those kids.
Yeah. Well, you know, it
ain't your case no more, so...
But, you know, don't
you worry, Linden.
I'll get a ride. Oh,
I won't. Good luck.
Yeah. And good
luck in, uh, San Diego.
And tell the little
man I said, you know.
Yeah, definitely.
Oh, the cops didn't bother
to clean up after themselves.
And they broke that
vase that Ma gave you.
Let's go play in your
room, boys, come on.
Hey, he said to go play in the
room. You have to come too.
Come on. Let's go.
Yeah, well I'm older.
Stop arguing. Go.
Uh, Terry, I'll do that.
You need to go to work.
I'm not going, Mitch. Geez.
Here. Use some bleach.
Why didn't you call her?
I mean, all weekend.
Hey, look, it's the cute cop.
Oh, my God.
My God, are you smoking pot?
Oops. You caught me.
Aren't you, like, a cop?
Do you want a hit?
I'm off the clock. It's not
like I'm gonna arrest you.
Whatever.
Okay.
Go to it, little girl.
Do it again.
You didn't inhale.
Hold it.
Now let it go.
Let it go.
That's some crazy, sick
weed. I'm so stoned right now.
Yeah. Is that right?
Yeah, totally.
So are we gonna party?
Yeah.
What?
How old are you?
Old enough.
Yeah, all right.
Here, you keep
it. I gotta bounce.
Wait.
There's no place to
party here, princess.
I know a place.
In the basement. The cage.
The cage?
Hey!
Hey, aren't we gonna party?
See the world. Uh, I am just...
If we stay through the weekend, I can
go to Nash's party. What's the big deal?
The big deal is you're supposed
to start school tomorrow.
And Rick is waiting for us.
For you, you mean.
What's going on with you, Jack?
Nothing.
I know how hard
this move is for you.
How much you're
giving up. I get it.
But it's gonna be great.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
We leave for the
airport in five minutes.
Let's get there early so I
can score some duty-free cigs.
- Jack okay?
- How'd you raise four of 'em?
Had a wife.
Maybe I need one
of those. What's that?
Uh, coroner's report
on the Larsen girl.
Cause of death was drowning.
T.O.D. anywhere from
Friday through to Monday.
Tough call 'cause of the water.
Ditto on whether or not she was raped.
Rosie was alive when
that car went in the water.
And it takes, what, 10
minutes to fill a trunk that size?
Ripped off her own fingernails
trying to claw her way out.
I'm not staying.
Well, you better get goin' then.
I'll have one of the
guys drive you and Jack.
Hey, Jackie boy, how you
doin', huh? You wanna go?
Ohh! Doo! Ohh! You had me.
Request available C.S.U. unit,
600 block of Orland Avenue,
Fort Washington High School.
We'll call in our E.T.A.
Load it up.
Tomorrow, look
for periods of rain and
a high of 45 degrees.
And now, back to the news desk.
With 25 days left
before the election,
three-term incumbent Mayor
Lesley Adams holds a small lead...
ahead of City Council
President and challenger
Darren Richmond in
the race for Seattle may...
Mitch?
Where's Mom?
I don't know. I'm
hungry. When's dinner?
Yitanes is gonna try to do all the
talking, so you gotta drown her out, right?
You got your bullet points?
S.E.I.U. is the heart of the
city. The machinists built it.
You are Seattle, the
real Seattle, et cetera.
You're gonna do great.
Tonight is your night.
Yeah, I guess so.
Hello. This is Darren
Richmond. Who is this?
I have no comment.
Yes. Yes, I'm sure.
That was a reporter...
wanting confirmation that the Larsen
girl was found in our campaign car.
You missed your plane? Again?
What is this place?
It's where the real
Halloween party went down.
♪♪
English - US - LINE 21