No!
Yeah. Linden here.
Back behind the tape.
Yeah, you heard me.
Sarah. Sorry about this.
Lieutenant said you were on call, so...
Where's the body? Conveyor shed.
Homeless guy found
her a couple hours ago.
Jane Doe. No I.D., wallet.
Coroner's en route.
You're the first one here.
Gotta go up the stairs.
Follow the ramp.
You'll find her.
You want me to walk you
through? No, I'm good, thanks.
You're outta here, what,
Friday? Nope. Today.
Hey, hey!
♪ For she's a
jolly good fellow ♪
♪ Which nobody can deny ♪♪
Yeah!
All right! Give her...
Give her a glass.
Rick, are you still here?
Rick?
Boo. I so had you.
Uh-uh. Charlie Brown with the
football. I think Lucy needs a spanking.
No! No!
I'm not even gonna ask.
Where's Jack? Dropped
him off at school.
Is he mad?
He's 13. It's his
job to hate us.
He'll come around.
Or I'll make him.
What does Candy Cane
feel about Sonoma?
Pop that damn thing
before Jack sees it.
Okay.
What time are the
movers coming? In an hour.
Regi called. Said she wanted to take Jack
for a spin on the boat before you leave.
Maybe she can give
me away at the wedding.
What'll your parents
think about that?
Who cares? What about you?
You ready to do this? Do what?
Sell the condo. Quit your job.
Move your kid away
from his cool friends.
Marry me.
You know I'm not one for words.
It's a good thing. I
only need two of 'em.
Mmm. That's me.
Why can't you fly
down with us tonight?
Candy Cane wants
to play. Yeah? Okay.
Tickets on top of the
fridge. Flight's at 9:30.
- I do.
- What?
Want to marry you.
Tickets on the
fridge. Flight's at 9:30.
No, I'll have a few
hours before the airport.
It would be great to
take Jack on the water.
Bad door. Wh-What
are you doin' here?
Uh, who... Can I help you?
- Yeah. This is my office.
- Who are you?
I'm Holder from
County. Oh, you Linden?
Sar, you there?
Yeah. I gotta go. I'll
see you tonight, Regi.
Yeah, I'm Linden. I thought
you'd be outta here by now.
If you need more time, I
can wait outside. It's okay.
No, no. Come on
in. I'm almost done.
Damn it. Okay, I got it.
Oh, that guy.
There you are.
So I hear you're moving to L.A.
San Francisco area.
Um, Oakland? Sonoma.
Sonoma. That's nice.
Yep.
Nice weather. Ocean. Beaches.
Hate that shit.
You must love this place then.
Ouch.
Crackhead thought
she was Picasso?
Crackhead's
six-year-old son drew it.
- He get iced too?
- No.
So what happened to the kid?
You don't waste time
moving in, do you?
No. County cut
me loose early, so...
Well, you got a
tough act to follow.
You wrapped up here,
Sarah? Yep. All done.
Good. Got a call down at
Discovery Park. Check it out.
On my last day? My flight's
tonight. You're still on the city's dime.
You can hand it off end of
shift, 6:00. Go on, do your job.
Take him. Show him
how to work a scene.
I know how to work a scene.
Grab a box. We'll take my car.
All right. Over there.
They tapped me out of
the academy first year.
Boom. Straight to Undercover.
So I was working Vice, Narco.
I don't know, I guess Narco
kind of stuck to me, so...
You? U.C.?
I never would have guessed.
Whatever.
It's mostly like
street-level buys and busts.
You know, Joaquin shooting
Rahim. Blah, blah, blah.
You think Homicide's
gonna be any different?
Well, at least
you got a bad guy.
Yeah? Who's that?
Is that why you're
runnin' away, Linden?
'Cause you don't know no more?
Detective Linden.
Where's the body? Still looking.
Schoolkids on a field trip
this morning found this.
This park's like
tweaker central at nights.
Ho bags bringing
their tricks down.
- Could be some base head.
- Owner's not an addict.
At least not the kind
who hangs around here.
It's a wool sweater.
Looks recently cleaned.
- Brought it to
the coin wash. So what?
- You dry-clean wool.
Do you know any tweakers who
drop their wardrobe off at the cleaner's?
Anything else?
This.
A.T.M. card.
"Stanley Larsen."
Guy loses his wallet while
he's getting his knob polished.
Anyway, um, keep
looking. Search the field.
You find anything else,
mark it, don't move it.
And call in Sex Crimes.
This is theirs for now.
Yo, we got here first.
Yeah, and we don't
got a body. Not yet.
You want to follow it up, go
for it. You're my ride, Linden.
So I'll drop you off at the
station. I need to finish packing up.
I thought you were done.
Flight's not till 9:00, right?
I won't let you
miss it. Promise.
Let's have a talk with
this Stanley Larsen.
What's that stink?
We're here for the pickup.
I'm Stan Larsen. Yes. Come.
Place gives me the creeps. Hey,
Belko. He can hear you, Belko.
Osama don't give a
shit. Do you, Osama?
What'd I tell you?
See? Take. Take.
Great. Thanks for your help.
My name Feza, not Osama.
I'll bring your
paperwork by tomorrow.
Shut up, Stan.
Hey, babe. Stan, you
need to get home right now.
Okay. You know what?
That's gonna stay broken,
no matter how many times
you wave that roll of tape at it.
We can't afford a new
one. I'll get Belko to fix it.
You know what? I am in no mood
for that "Belko will fix it" bullshit.
Oh, there we go. Good as new.
Don't even look at that
"on" button, Stanley Larsen.
I've still got the
touch, ukochana.
Oh, yeah? Oh, yeah?
No! No! Huh? Huh?
You're all wet! Get off of me!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
No! No! No. No.
You are in such trouble! No.
You are useless.
Get off of me.
Ah! No. Shut up!
Come here.
I gotta go.
Okay. Bye.
Come here, come here, come here.
I want to talk to you about something.
Yeah?
You got to promise
me you won't blow.
I mean it. Tell me, baby.
Rosie said she'd
apply for colleges.
She just wants
to go out of state.
Baby, that is a good thing, come
on, that she finally wants to go.
Well, if it's what she wants.
Of course it is, Stan. I'm not
getting into this with you again.
Mitch, out of state.
Isn't she kind of young?
She's almost 18. You've gotta
let her grow up sometime, Papa.
I'll think about it.
Okay.
Stan, gotta move.
Okay, one more time.
Right here on the stairs.
Stop being such a devil.
You ready? Yeah, let's do it.
Jamie.
Well, I'm just on my way.
Hey, Darren. Good
morning. Hey, how are you?
Councilman Richmond.
Times poll just came in. Adams
closed our three-point lead.
Good morning to you too, James.
Election's in 26 days. We don't
have time to be jerking off here.
Wow. Not an image
I want in my head.
Where were you? I, uh, slept in.
You never sleep in. I did
this morning. I lost my watch.
Which you took?
No. It's mine. It looks
like yours, but it's mine.
What time do we leave
for the school, Jamie?
Ten till. I'll
gather the troops.
He's more nervous than I am.
And you're surprised by this?
What have we here?
Looks vaguely like a man's
timepiece. Wherever did you find it?
On my kitchen table.
What was it doing there?
With the recent mall
shootings, the press is
gonna hammer Mayor
Adams on the gang issue.
- Give 'em ammo.
- He killed my midnight
hoops tourneys...
and after-school programs
four years in a row.
That's easy.
"Now we have kids stealing and
dealing we could have turned around."
You write that? Jamie did.
- That's not bad.
- Mall shooters? Recent
gang inductees. Somalis.
Adams was a fool to
ignore them last election.
He'll pay for it
this time around.
Sixty thou and growing. Registration
in Rainier Valley's through the roof.
You get them to
vote, we got a shot.
Forum today could
be our turning point.
I had an interesting chat with
Councilwoman Yitanes this morning.
- Ruth is talking to you?
- Not only that,
she's endorsing me.
What?
We go public tomorrow. Until
then, we keep it under wraps.
The only way we get the
unions is with her vote.
- Add that to the Somalis...
- The election's ours.
Hey. Seattle P.D. We're
lookin' for a Stanley Larsen.
He's not here. You his wife?
- Yeah.
- Do you know
where we can find him?
Uh, he's on a job. I don't know
where. What about last night?
Why are you asking about Stan?
Does your husband usually
go out at night, Mrs. Larsen,
and not tell you where? No. Stan's
always home with me and the kids.
Last night too? Yeah.
We got home late from a
camping trip, so he was here.
Have him call us
when he gets in.
Are you sure he
stayed in last night?
Yep, I'm sure. How?
How do you think?
We just wait for
this prick to call?
In situations like this, I like to ask
myself, "What would Jesus do?"
Don't know. I'll ask him.
Mrs. Larsen, do
you have a daughter?
Yeah. Why?
Did she go on that
camping trip too?
No. She stayed here for the
weekend. She stayed at a friend's house.
When did you talk to her last?
Um, Friday,
right before we left town.
Why?
Did you see Rosie and Cameron?
All right. Settle down, guys.
We don't have a lot of time today.
You guys got your questions
ready for the candidates?
Yeah? Did anyone do their
reading? Anyone? Anyone?
- Sterling?
- What?
Your question or your
cell phone... your call.
I'm looking for Rosie Larsen.
Um, yeah, totally. Rosie
spent the weekend at my house.
Did she come to school with you?
Like, I have a zero
period, and I left early,
so maybe she slept in.
I don't know.
Sterling, are you okay?
Oh, sorry. It
happens all the time.
Here. Uh, thank you.
Look, the candidates will be
here in less than half an hour.
Can you make sure the
seniors are seated by then?
Yeah, no problem, Ms. Meyers.
Nice try.
What?
I told you. How about
telling me the truth?
Rosie had dinner
with me and the boys...
and then she went to that
Halloween dance at her school...
at, I don't know, around 6:00.
6:00? That's the last time
you saw your daughter?
- Yeah.
- You recall
what she was wearing?
You know, tight
jeans and a sweater.
She said only freshmen wore
costumes. What color sweater?
I don't know. Pink.
Why are you asking about
her sweater, her clothes?
Your daughter have a history
of running away, Mrs. Larsen?
Rosie?
No, never. That's crazy.
- You have words
with her, a fight?
- No.
You weren't worried when you
didn't hear from her all weekend?
I told you, our phone
was out of range.
Christ, she's 17. It's not like
we left some little kid behind.
Hello.
Yeah.
I-I don't understand.
No, no, I heard you
the first time. I'm-I'm...
Yes.
Linden.
That was Rosie's school.
She wasn't with
Sterling this weekend.
Last anybody saw her
was on Friday, at the dance.
The press are falling all over
themselves. Those kids can't stay awake.
Adams knew I would come after him on
the gang thing, and he covered his bases.
Expect a countermove. It
doesn't take the shine off you.
So why tell me? Because
he's trying to shake you.
And obviously it's working.
What's really wrong?
Move in with me.
Avoiding my question.
And you're avoiding mine.
You can break hearts after
you get the single-female vote.
You are cold-blooded.
I know. That's my
job... taking care of you.
So take care of me. Move in.
Darren, I know where
you were this morning.
I wish you'd talk
to me about her.
Councilman. The police are here.
You should be aware that the
school is a potential abduction site.
We'll do our best to be
discreet with the media out there.
Surely this can
wait, Lieutenant.
We can hold off as long as
you feel it necessary, Mayor.
- Councilman?
- Can it wait... your investigation?
Missing kids are usually
killed in the first 72 hours,
so, no, it can't.
Well, then we'll have to cancel.
A missing child takes precedence.
Gwen, you can contact
my office to reschedule.
Is that it, Lieutenant?
I apologize for the inconvenience.
We'll keep you updated.
Let's go.
Darren.
I'd wager you were quite
the high school athlete.
I never cared much for games.
Councilwoman Yitanes does.
I wouldn't depend on
Ruth's word, if I were you.
Assembly's canceled.
Return to your classes. Everyone
check in with your homerooms, please.
Sterling isn't in class. I don't
know where she is. I'm sorry.
We'll need her home address.
Yeah, yeah. The office will have it.
You were chaperoning at
that Halloween dance, right?
- Yeah.
- Who was Rosie with?
Sterling, like always.
Did she leave with her too?
I didn't see. I
was busy trying...
- Do you recall
what she was wearing?
- Yeah. Yeah.
She was dressed up like a witch.
A witch?
Hat, wand, pink wig.
Most of these girls use
Halloween to play stripper,
so she kind of stood out.
Rosie... she was a pretty
hot piece though, right?
Yeah, I wouldn't know. She's 17.
Kind of my point.
Anyone hittin' that?
Yeah, I don't think
she had a boyfriend.
Ask Sterling.
Are we done here? Yeah.
Call if you think
of anything else.
Hmm.
Linden here. Is this
Jack Linden's mother?
Yeah. What is it?
This is his school calling.
We need you to come in.
Okay. I'll be there.
Put a car on Sterling's house.
Where are you going?
And get a K-9 unit out at
the park. I'll meet you there.
You're my ride, Linden.
♪♪
Kris.
Kris!
Kris, come on. Please.
What's up, Sterling?
Where's Jasper? He's not at
his house or school or anywhere.
Did he and Rosie
hook up this weekend?
And I should tell you, why?
'Cause the cops are looking for her.
She could be in
serious trouble. I mean it.
Give me a smoke.
He's on the island.
Weekend MOTS.
Parents are gone to Abu Dhabi
or some diseased hole like that.
Is Rosie with him?
Jasper scored some X.
So, yeah, he was
definitely looking to bone.
You're such an ass.
See ya, Sterling.
♪♪
Smoking cigarettes at
school? Really, Jack?
It's not like I was
doing crack, Mom. God.
Why do I have to sit
around at Regi's anyway?
Because there's nowhere
else to go, that's why.
Did you give our new
address to your friends?
Why would I do that? I
don't know. So they can write.
Hello? Facebook.
Kids don't write letters,
Mom. That's retarded.
Well, it'd be really great
for them to visit then.
Like that's ever gonna happen.
They'll love California. There's
so much to do. It'll be great.
Hey, Regi. Rick's
putting together a party.
Get some of the
neighborhood kids together.
He's not my dad.
Hang on.
- Linden here.
- Hey, it's me.
Yeah. What is it, Holder?
We got the K-9 unit here. We're
starting a sweep of the field.
Okay. I'll be there.
He's trying his best.
We're going to be really happy
in California. It's going to be great.
Jack. Huh?
I gotta go.
How you been?
All right. What's wrong?
Come on. Tell me.
Stan. Just call me, all right?
Rosie, we're home!
Mom, Rosie promised to
bring us biking at the docks.
Can we go, please,
please? Please?
Wow. Can't even hear myself think
here. What'd you feed 'em, Terry?
Bag of sugar with a Red Bull
chaser. And it was awesome.
Go put your backpacks away, and
Aunt Terry will give you more candy.
Awesome! Yes!
Rosie! Any word on Rosie?
No. And Stan's not
answering his phone.
- And what'd the cops say?
- Nothing.
They just asked me a
bunch of bullshit, as usual.
Mom! Mom.
Where is Rosie? She promised!
She promised we'd go biking.
She promised! Denny,
quit your yellin'. I mean it.
Rosie's still at school.
I'll take you. Go.
Go, get your helmets. Go.
Sorry. I'm just goin'
a little nuts right here.
I'm telling you, that girl's gettin' the
ass-kicking of her life when she gets home.
Look, don't worry.
She'll turn up.
Come on!
Stan.
Stan, listen. Um, it's Rosie.
Why'd she lie to us, and
where the hell has she been?
She still dating
that rich jackoff?
What, Jasper? No, she
broke up with him last summer.
Now Sterling's run off? Nobody can
find her? What the hell's going on?
Just stay here in case Rosie
comes back. I'm goin' out.
Stan, the cops were asking
about birthmarks and scars...
and jewelry and anything
they can identify her with.
So I told them about, you know,
that necklace she always wears,
that little butterfly necklace.
Why are they asking
about that? Hey. She's 17.
She's dumb. She's not thinking
about anybody but herself.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'll find her. Okay?
Okay.
What do you got?
K-9 picked up a scent.
It started at the fire road
where we found the sweater.
Looks like she ran a zigzag
through the field, ended up here.
You sweep for possible
burial sites? Yup. Nothin'.
I don't know. Maybe
she's not here.
Where's the map? The
dad's alibi checked out.
The park ranger logged
vehicle plates at the campsites.
The Larsens' car never left.
Did you have a talk with Dad?
He's not a suspect anymore.
You need to have a talk.
And get the unis to
do another sweep.
We did two, plus the dog.
Thought you wanted to
learn how to work a scene.
Been working it,
Linden, for hours.
Welcome to Homicide.
Clock never stops.
I thought you had a plane to catch.
Detective. We've got something.
Yeah. Linden here. What is it?
We've got a possible burial site,
northeast corner of the woods.
Adams announced his new anti-gang funding
package while we were at the school.
Great. Now it looks like
he was on board all along.
You shouldn't have canceled.
I didn't have a choice.
Wait a second. What if
we play into this thing?
Missing kid, desperate family.
You pulling out all the stops to
find her, campaign be damned.
This is perfect, Darren,
especially if the kid ends up dead.
- Jamie, shut up.
- Adams will look
like the douche bag...
I am not using a family
tragedy for a... a sound bite!
- He knew about
Yitanes's endorsement.
- What?
Are there any staff we
need to worry about?
Richmond. Darren, it's Meg.
The Times called. That reporter
again. He's asking questions.
I can't really talk right now.
This is important. He's asking
about when I worked for you.
He knows about your trips.
My trips are public record.
Not all of them.
Only you knew about those, Meg.
Gwen and Jamie knew about them,
too, and I'm not the one blabbing.
I've gotta go,
Darren. Thanks, Meg.
Hey, Jinxie Jo. How you doing?
Where is she?
Where's Rosie?
She didn't tell me, but
his parents are out of town.
And on Friday she got really
dressed up for the dance...
and she does that when
she's gonna meet him.
Jasper. She's at Jasper's
house, Mr. Larsen.
Stan.
Rosie's on the
island with that kid.
What, with Jasper? Are you sure?
Yep. I'm goin' to
pick her up now.
Oh, thank God.
No more worrying, okay, babe?
Yeah. Okay. Okay. Love you.
Ohh.
Yeah.
Found the Larsen
girl, with her boyfriend.
- Her friend gave it up.
- Sterling?
- Holder put a car on her.
- No, he didn't.
And I didn't authorize you
to bring in a K-9 unit either.
Did you talk directly
to the Larsen girl?
Some teenybopper got
laid. End of story. It's over.
And don't you got
a plane to catch?
Linden. Got something.
Oh.
Mama.
Wrap it up. We're done.
Where is she? Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You need to leave right now,
or I'm gonna call the cops.
Where the hell is my daughter?
She's not here. She's not here.
Rosie! She's not here.
You can't go up there!
She's not here.
She's not here. Rosie.
Rosie, get up. We're
goin' home now!
See?
Told you Rosie isn't here.
Uh, negative. At
this time it looks like...
Let's go, Linden!
Hey, babe. I'm thinking pizza.
How about we grab a couple pies after
I pick you and Jack up from the airport?
That sounds great, Rick.
I had this sick idea
for Sunday's barbecue.
Jack's going to be
bored out of his skull...
- What's the holdup?
- Give me a minute!
So I'm gonna get one of
those Bounce-A-Rama things...
You said that 20 minutes ago!
Throw him in there with other kids.
Let them bounce the crap out of each
other while the "grown-ups" get wasted.
Come to think about it, I
might jump in there myself.
No judgments, right?
Let's go. Let's go!
You there, Sarah?
I think I'm losing
you, babe. Hello?
Hello!
Sarah?
Where does the
fire road lead to?
To Puget Sound. Why?
Sarah. Rick, I gotta
go. I'll call you later.
They found her, Linden.
How far is the Sound from here?
Way on the other
side of the park, okay?
The Larsen girl ran in
the opposite direction.
So where are they
going with fishing poles?
There's a lake
on the other side.
Hello?
Mitch. Mitch, Rosie
wasn't with him.
Stop it! Mom!
What? Where is she?
I don't know. I'm at the park.
Why?
You said they found
her sweater here, right?
Mommy. I-I don't
know that that was hers.
Mom. What's wrong, Mom?
Tom, go watch
your videos. Go on.
Yes! Why does
he always get to...
Go. Now.
Stan, she wouldn't
be at that park.
I don't know where
else to go, Mitch.
Why are you there? I don't
understand. What is going on?
Can you open the trunk?
Be advised. Forensics
team is on scene.
What is it? What's
going on, Stan?
Stan?
Stop! Stop now!
What are you doing? I need
you to get back in your truck, sir.
I need you to get back in
there and move your truck.
Stan!
Wait, wait. Can I help you, sir?
Stan, what's going
on? Please, sir.
Move back. Hey.
Rosie!
Calm down. Step back.
Detective, we've
got the father here.
Rosie!
Calm down. Just
let me talk to her.
Just let me talk to her.
Okay, okay, okay.
You can't be here, Mr. Larsen.
Is it my daughter?
I'm sorry. You can't be here.
Oh, my... No, no.
No, no! Rosie!
Rosie!
Just move back to the truck.
Stan!
Stan! Stan?
That's my baby girl!
Stan!
I ran the plates.
Car belongs to the
Richmond campaign.
Richmond?
City Councilman Richmond?
English - US - Line 21