400 BC
NagaDutta : Vishnugupta, what is dharma?
Vishnugupta Chankya : Dharma is doing what is necessary
Today
Yo Chittu, you continue..
Chittu: It's a simple matter
Say you are in a train..
And you see a nice lady with a kid
You start the conversation by playing with the kid
Where ever you start, it's always gonna end in 2 topics
Politics and cinema
You start with "What is the last film you saw?"
Now, you ask the most important question
'You like Rajinikant  or Kamal Hasan?'
Machi, that's the main matter.
That's how I had gotten haid with many ladies...
If they like Rajini, let them be
But if the like Kamal...then she is a horny one.. an easy lay!
We can easily work those flirts
Why is that?
Kamal looks sexy to them
Simple technique.. works with unknown woman.
Make her cry somehow....
Console her ...  screw her!
Hey Sappa ( looser) !
Looser.. why are you so Sappa (Looser) ?
Have you done anything in life?
Look at our Ayya!
Even at his age, he keeps up with an young girl
The old man doesn't trust us with her
But he trusts you
Why?
Because you are a sappa (Looser)
Pasupathy: Hey Sappa, go buy me a tea
I bought it already
OK, buy one more
Hey
You stay here
A mule has come from Rameswaram
- What is it?
Powdered cocaine
Market rate is ₹20,000,000
He is willing to sell for ₹5,000,000
- Why?
- His sister loves me?
It's not his
He is just a mule
He is not happy with his cut
So he want to sell it for ₹5,000,000 and settle in life
- Whose is it?
Gajendran's
- He will fuck our shit out
Let him
Hey Pashupati !
Hey, he will try..
But we are also not gonna be quiet
We can manage
If the stuff is in our hands
.. then we can control the business for some time
We can go back to what we were...
Risky
Its a .... good deal
Hah !
Why? Are you a limp dick now?
Grandpa has gone limp
Can I speak my mind?
Lend me ₹5,000,000, I will take care of the business
The risk is all mine.
Now on, I will take over such risky businesses
We will split the profits 50-50
What do you think?
We do the deal tomorrow...
(yes)
Hey..
- call the Marwari Seth
- He will give a 'five millions'
- Go fetch it
- You first check the stuff
- We will think about percentage later
- Pasupathy
Go
- I am no limp dick
- Still got it
Go
Mayilvaganam Sir, we are here
Who's doing this business? Ayya or you?
No clue..... That is Ayya's style
Chittu: You kept running your mouth
We shit our pants, didn't know what to do there
'you didn't know what to do'?
Do as Ayya tells you to!
You do work for him..
Bark if you dress up as a dog
(on phone)Yeah, tell me Kasthuri!
I am coming
I am on a job
Pasupathy, what's with all the crowd?
♪ (Ponmeni uruguthey from Moondram Pirai)♪
Isn't it a good song?
I love this vamp (Actress Silk Smitha) with a golden heart !
Poor girl! Untimely death. Why did she hang her ?
(Pasupathy) Sir, where is the stuff?
They told me that cocaine has arrived. The place...It's some name....
...It's in the tip of my tongue. But it's not coming out of me yet....
Do you know why?
Bava lodge
Are you gonna snatch it?
Don't know
Sir, can you keep this quiet?
Chittu: Pasupathy, I thought he was Gajendran's man?
Hay ! You think he is a thug?
He is a police sub-inspector
If there is money, he will work for anyone
What is he saying about me?
Nothing bad, you carry on boss
Do you realize whose stuff it is?
Sir, A good drink is never without a stink.
hay
You know about Gajendran, don't you?
He is a Son of Bitch. Better watch your ass.
Gagendra Gajendra..What's all this fuss about Gajendran?
Master, 5 teas!
Let me tell you a story
15 years back..
Gajendran and Gajapathy were peaking in their import/export business
There was this guy, related to them....
Brother-in-law?
A distant brother-in-law
He was working as a mule for them
In a deal...
...instead of 10 pieces only 8 showed up
Gajendran had a big doubt on the mule
He brought mule's whole family...
- ... and kicked the piss out
- His own brother-in-law?
ha, that's mean shit
Right in front his family...
... broke his fucking face
Then he poured boiling oil on him..
...the skin started peeling off
His kids are crying out loud now
His wife is hysterical
After all that, he still sticks to his story
Now comes the plot twist
A call comes in..
...for Gajendran
'Boss, the stuff is all alright'
'It was a packing mistake..'
'The Mule's hands are clean'
...and the call ended.
The beaten up mule is now staring at Gajendran
Gajendran slowly took out a knife out of his pocket..
...and sliced open mule's throat
The blood gushed out like flush water
Mule was dead
Why he did that?
'After all this torture today...'
'...if he gets a chance tomorrow...'
'...and the knife turns around...'
'..that's why!'
Now brother Gajapathy goes to the wife...
'It was a unknowing mistake..'
'.. was just a business misunderstanding'
'So, don't bring it up ever'
He even apologized to her
Now Gajendran walks to the wife ...
...takes her hand like he is consoling her..
..and says 'Don't let anyone know'...
..takes her hand to his mouth..
...and bites the fucking thumb off her hand.
'She agreed not to say a word'
'Then, why did you bite the finger?'
... asks Gajapathy
'After she speaks, it's no use in chopping fingers '
That's Gajendran
The girl never came back in town after
Just with his teeth?
I have heard a story about a vanishing ghost hitchhiker
Ask if they have seen it, they will reply 'no'
But his acquaintance's acquaintance had seen it
This is just a built up legend
...and you fell for it
You only look smart..
..but you are dumb ass
Bava Lodge
Mule: That's all Kalaiya. I bring the goods
Deliver and get ₹10,000 for that
After that, for 2 months..
..drinks and cuties
Bring the goods again
Deliver
Drinks and cuties
You can't believe me?
See this
(Kalaiyan) The cutie is not that cute
...but she still makes me jealous of you... you are my hero.
No! I am afraid
If you get caught, you are a jelly....gone
So, I have decided..
I am not giving it this time
Instead
I am giving it to these guys
They have tricked by throwing just 10,000 at me
I didn't know about it's worth
Or How much you get here?
15,000?
20,000?
That much?
What is in here?
Like X-ray goggles?
Can we see everything through the clothes?
hmm, you will see nothing
All lights are out
You will feel nothing
It's white man's snuff - heavy
I am settled for life with this
WoW! A drink to that, lets celebrate...
One for me?   oh this is mine
(Kodukkapuli) Haven't moved it's lazy ass...Chi !
Hey Kalaiya
Why is Kodukkapuli pissed?
Is he yelling at the cock or me?
I have the same question
Hey Kodukkapuli
Feed the cock it will be hungry now
Mind your fucking business
He is a funny talker
Funny talker
A kid is cursing at you, do you have no shame?
What's the shame in it?
He is my son.. my own blood
My son Kodukkapuli...
Curse a few swear words at your dad
He won't curse now, that's the technique
He is just like his mom
Fair skinned , wavy hair...
.. and a proud person
I gambled away all my fortunes..
.. that's why he is angry
Aaaaa !
No, I may not look that way
I am from a Zamindar(aristocrat) family
Someone just bought my palace to make it a hotel
Idiots
I lost everything
At last, I opened a small store
I gave away the goods on credit
When I went asking for money..
They replied, 'How can an aristocrat ask money?'
I couldn't insist on returning the money...
....from those poor peasants
But I couldn't leave it at that
Then, I borrowed ₹2,000 to buy more goods...
.. but it was some kind of rocket interest loan
The lender is now asking for ₹5,000 to payoff
Now, threatening too
Where do I go for that much money?
That's why, we brought the cock here
Now, after Kaattu Munieswaran, he is our family deity
This Kaalayan's last treasure
After he wins today, I am going to settle all debts
... and save my family
Come here my golden goose
(Kudukkapulli) Chi, Don't touch my rooster.
It's actually his rooster
To me, he is my son.
For him, the rooster is his son
If it were mine, I would have sold and gotten drunk
Kaalaya, whom did you borrow the money from?
From Varaagamoorthy
That asshole?
If he doesn't get back the money...
... he sells their wives and kids for prostitution
Aai !
So, it is for real?.. it is for real?
Does it really happen?
I didn't listen to anyone's advice back home
You came from nowhere and you know what he does
I had no clue
Everything is lost
Drink up, all will be well
Drink, don't worry
You don't think it will happen?
Don't worry
You! who talks like that?
Act like a grown man
OK, stop drinking. Listen to the grown up there.. you moron
Your son is angry
He is annoyd
I am proud
I have a room
I am leaving
Kodukkapuli, I will see you later
Bye Kaalaya
So wasted ..... so wasted ..... so wasted
Get up ... quick
Fighting is unethical..
Getting late for the fight
Pa ! Wake up!
Shut up and move....
Lift your hand. The other one
Turn around
Say Aaaa
- Please take him to his room
- OK
- Please go
Vanakkam Ayya
Ayya, there's 5 in here
♪ (RJ talking on radio) ♪
♪ (Oru naalukkul ethanai kanavu) ♪
Hey Sappa! (Looser)
The dumb whore Subbu is crying upstairs
Buy whatever she needs
Take her wherever she asks you to
Keep this money
Ask her not to cry
A look on her face, and I go limp...
(TV playing)
(Disney Channel playing 'Power Rangers')
Hey Subbu! look here.. Magic Magic...
Don't feel bad that he hit you. He is a good man
A good man?
I am young enough to be his grand kid
He tricked me to be his mistress
And you call him good man?
Earlier he couldn't do it..
....to hide that he beat me
And you call him good?
You were upset...
..was trying to console you
Subbu: Piss off fool........
Sorry
That's why I am 'Sappa' (fool) and no one likes me
But I really like you
Why?
Because you are like me...
Don't cry...........don't cry........don't cry
- You need some talent for that
- (on phone) I am in Madras now
If I walk on the streets...
I can get both the girl and her mom
(on phone) Don't fuss. I will come home for dinner.
I will come home at night
Let me tell you something
I have seduced many ladies
But there is one, I want to screw really...
... our Subbu
(on phone) Hey wear that red sari
Why are you looking at me like that?
Don't you have that idea?
Will you kick her off the bed?
Well, he is a loyal husband.
You don't wish that?
Everyone staring as if I am a pervert.
She is a poor girl!
I am also thinking about her with love and affection.
I do really like her
Ayya tricked her by promising she will be a movie star
I have liked her since then
Hey ! Pardon me you high Sirs.
(on phone) OK stop talking and cut the phone
Anna(bro), is it new girl friend?
No, boy friend .... dick head
oh, he is pissed.
Let me see your phone
What is this shit phone- fossils ..?
There are way better phones now
Colour phone, video phone speaker phone,...
Why do you have it?
- Why do I need that?
- Why?
In a video phone, you can watch actress showering
What can you see in that tiny screen? Give it back
Ok, atleast a color or speaker phone is bare necessacity?
Why do you need a speaker? Are you deaf?
Enlighten him!
Look at our Chittu
When ladies speak to him, we listen to it on speaker
Some say- You are super....
'You are the best, my husband is nothing'....
Don't they know it's on speaker?
The ones falling for him?
They all have to be dumb
Don't talk bad about them, Pasupathy
It's not about being dumb or sharp. It's technology
Let me put this call on speaker..
If they don't find it out...
You have insulted me and my herem..
... you are buying beer for all of us
Why beer for everyone?
You insulted me before them, so you should.....
Sir, Sir, please get the phone
They wouldn't mind, lets bet on it
Ok
Dude! beer for all...
Shhh. It's Ayya
- Yeah, what's up?
- (male voice) Are you busy?
No, I am not
(Ayya) Why didn't you answer, nasty cunt?
It was in my pocket so it took a while
Where are the goods?
Baba Lodge
Have you gone past the police checkpost?
Not yet
OK, kill Pasupathy before the checkpost
Aren't we all friends?
Then, why the cunt-hair you tooled up?
if you are a dog... you bark ..
A dog can also wag his tail...
Chitoo ! Hide the tools
Fuck !
Play some song. You - knife to his side
Be relaxed but vigilant
♪ (Kaattu Vazhi Pora Ponne - Malaiyor Mambattiyan) ♪
Licence ?
- Where to?
- Pondichery
- Have you been drinking?
- Sir, we haven't gone to Pondy yet
Go Go
- Hey asshole, what if we are drunk?
- What did you say?
- You can't stick up your finger if you want to
- What did you say? Get down
- I am asking you cuntcopper
- Hey, keep quiet!
Pasupathi shut up !
Hey, leave me. Lets see what he can do
Asshole
Get down.. Get down
Sir, he is Rainman type. We are taking him for treatment.
Hey, you leave..
...grab him too. Grab him
I have a political clout!
You can't do a shit...
I am Ayya's man
One slap and he will forget that he is a cop..
Sir, he is mad.. please forgive him..
Hay ! Tell Ayya that 'No one can do shit to Pasupathy'
You don't worry Pasupathy...
..we will pick up Kasturi from your home
Sir Sir Sir .... please sir.... please si....I was wrong Sir....
Please let me go... Please!...Please let me go... Please!
Asshole !  Where were these "Sirs" few minutes back?
Stop staring
(Prayers to Kaattu Muneswaran) Gods of the sky...Gods of the forests...Gods of the Rain....... bless us..............
Bless us .............................
Slutty cunt!  Lazy bitch...
Stab him, don't leave him alone... you whore
Don't run away bitch...fight...don't give in...Fight fight
My royal pride is being fucked. Fight bitch!
Who is that joker?
Shut up... you are not the one who is fighting .....
Keep silence
Whoring slut, go fight...Shit eating whore
Donkey piss drinking cock, continue fighting
Showed up with his shinning armor and sword
See my cock growling.. its ok, you only lost to kaalayan's rooster..
its ok...
get lost
See the arrogance of the man... despite looser,
I told you so! You assholes laughed at me
Hide your face up your ass. Eat my shit..
(on phone) What the fuck happened?
Don't feel bad.
Pashpati has escaped.
You can say you lost to Kaalaiyan's cock, they will get it
oH oH ! Old man's cock has gone down! Oh! Old Cock..... limp cock---
Oh dead cock ..... oh oh limp cock........... oh oh Old cock.......................
Old cock! It's an old cock!
How he escaped?
Hey ! how can you? how can you?
Pa...(Dad)
He will have to return to save Kasthuri
Where is Kasturi ?
With me..
Don't bring her home. He will come there first..
Because that's where he will check first
Top off your tank and keep driving around the city
Don't stop anywhere for long
It will raise suspision
Hey ! Don't answer the phone unless I call
Let Pasupathy come, I will wait
Ok
- Is Kasthuri any trouble?
- No
Then don't give her any trouble either
Go home
Hey.. Go home
Subbu!
Do you like Rajini or Kamal?
Why? Are you trying to seduce me?
Everything has happened already, so answer me
Kamal or Rajini?
You tell me
Kamal, he is the king of love!
He french kisses all actresses
In the movie 'Hey Ram', .....
.... he bites both actresses' asses
- But I like Vijayakanth
- Why?
He is the one who always saves India from Pakistan
He gets justice no matter who does wrong
If a lady is in danger, he will risk a big fight
OK. Can you choose between Rajini and Kamal?
Kamal
Hey, aren't you lying for me?
So, Rajini?
- Why?
- Because he is Rajini
- Which is your favorite movie?
- Baashha
kya ?
We all would think that he was a common person...
... but Rajini was Baashaa, the don
Just like me!
Everyone thinks I am a 'Sappa'...
...only you know the real me
(whispers) Is it Ayya?
I didn't think I will ever see you alive
Get lost.... ass....cunt waxer
- hey, why are you cursing me?
- I asked you to shut your foul mouth
- What did I do?
- Why did you touch my chicken?
After we won, what's the need for that victory song?
He killed him, because he was pissed at you
I swear on you, I did nothing. You saw it didn't you?
It hurts
oh my child, why are you crying?
We lost..... lost it...... lost everything
Someone is going to sell our poor mom and sister
They are so innocent
No. None of that will happen
Our Kattumuni god wouldn't let that happen
Your dad is here!
You are a wastrel loser
I can't bear if you too call me that
Dad, hold this. Let us leave now
- Did you steal this?
- No
- Then? Did he give it to you?
- No, I took it
- Hey, that's wrong
- In our situation, nothing is wrong
Hey !
He was planning to settle down with this
I am begging you, lets leave
He bought us liquor, he is like a god
- We shouldn't betray him
- Leave me!!
Dad, don't go. You will get caught
Retard
Hey ! Why did you kill him?
No, he is sleeping
He is not breathing. He is dead.
- You stealer, you must have killed him!
- I didn't. He kept on drinking with you, you killed him!
- I didn't kill him
- Then, why will I kill him?
Came here....showed compassion...
He drank... smoked...
Left us in a jiffy. I can't understand
Dad, I can understand
What do you understand?
In our village....
...when our lost cow, came back what did gradma say?
'Our god Kattumuni brought it back'
This is given to us by Kattumuni
He couldn't bear our suffering...
... he came through someone's body...
gave the goods...the details...and left
Have we seen this guy before?
Then why did he show up and give us this?
You still don't believe it? See what we have offered
Oh, that is Kattumuni
Lets go, religious rioter!
Why are you in a hurry?
Nah..
God is with us
From today, all debts are gone. Worries gone.
Ache gone. Agony gone. Misery gone.
Go..Go...Go..
Brother, it's not here.
Go check again
I searched well
The deal we heard about with Pasupathy, must be true
If you were alive now.... I would have killed you
Hello
What the fuck ? Fucker not talking.. fucking fuck?
Hello hello
It has been a long time
Singapermal! Why did you steal my drugs?
Whose drugs are those?
Reply
It's mine
Whose mule brought it?
He is mine too
But I heard Pasupathy is going to steal it
I will not take it..
Got it ?
Pasupathi took it ?
Correct..
Is it Pashupathy's number ?
No
Sorry wrong number
Motherfucker
Told you
Gajapathy: Hey! Do you think I am a dumb fuck
- who will suck my own dick ?
I will kill you all ... you don't know me
Hey Gajapathi.
Do you know its value ? Fuckers I will massacre you all..
Everyone knows about your brother Gajendran's reputation
Doesn't make a fucking difference if he took or you did
I did'nt take it..
Pasupathi took it..
Hey! you fucking with me? How does it matter who took it?
He is your guy..
Was my man.....Not anymore..
Ok Ok .. I will kill him
Go ahead.. be a man..
I will buy you a lolipop.
Hey ! This is Mullu's area, right? Ask him to kill Pasupathi.
He has got the cocaine.
Then let him grab the cocaine before killing him.
But Mullu is not reliable..
I know. Just get the Pasupathi killed. Go
Singapermal ! If the two of you are conning me,
or even if I get a doubt that you are, I will fuck you all..
Hey Gajapathi ! you know about me..
Trust me...
If not,  then come over... we will sort it out like man
Gajendra does'nt have the stuff...
Nor does Pasupathi..
Ask our men to search the lodge...
Sir..
It should be at the lodge... bring it to me
By then, Gajendran would have killed Pasupathy
Killing 3 birds with one stone
Drugs in our hands... one bird
Yes
Gajendran killing Pasupathy... second bird............Hun
What's the third bird?
That is You dumb ass
Go.. Do your work...
Did you see?
Your buddies came and picked her up
When?
It has been a while
Son of a whore!
what's with the swearing?
I genuinely asked something...
...first you tried to kill me
Now, you have taken Kasthuri
You shouldn't have done that... Singaperumal
Eat all you can ..
..drink..
Motherfucker.... your mom's... this is your last day
...firstly, try to save your own ass
You are fucked up !
Mullu
Where's the stuff?
Hey ! I am dealing with a different problem
Hey ! I don't know
- I am talking here... why did you do that?
- He doesn't understand reason... kill him
- Don't give me orders, do as I say
- Just give me a spanner...
Kasthuri is in danger..
Singaperumal is trying to kill me
Gajendran's men are chasing to get me
Gajendran is pissed off.....
Tension... tension... tension...
Relax Bachhaaaaaaa !!!!!
Buddha had Bodhi tree...
To a gangster... it's the chase..........Nirvana!
The fear of being killed by whom and when is no more
Because, he is going to kill...
... and he is killing me now....
NOW
Now, I am not running alone
...my death is running along
After meeting death face to face..
..I have no confusion
Fuck...
My mind is all clear
If they took Kasthuri, to make me go there....
... she will be alive till I get there.
For now, Kasthuri is safe
Till they get the drugs, they won't kill me
.... till then I am safe as well
Next problem - Singaperumal
He is a heavy weight
I can't do anything alone
Enemy's enemy is a friend
Ayya taught me that
Gajendran is Ayya's enemy
He is a heavy weight too
But his son-of-the-whore are chasing me
Think. Think. Think.
In a day, when friends become enemies...
What does an enemy become?
Shoot me or leave me
Ae..Why did you buy me a samosa?
he..he..
Because I love you
What!
Always?...playing games,,
What is this?
♪ (Super Mario Bros. music) ♪
what if we go to a different world..................
Just like in the game.... ...
No Ayya to trouble us...
When you were playing it, that's what I was thinking
We don't have to go that far..lets go to Bombay
Oh yeah.
Ayya does'nt mean shit there
Dawood Bhai is the big shot there
After we reach Bombay, we buy a 30th floor apartment
where we can see the whole city
Also a car... a red one
But I will drive
Subbu, can you drive a car ?
No
But I will learn
But, we will need money for all that
...we got none
I will become a day laborer to make a living
No need. we will survive
No. If we go Bombay, we should be rich and live in luxury...
May be I will become a Hindi cinema heroine...
... you become my manager
No need
Hey ! I know. You are jealous now?
You don't want any other men to touch me
Idiot, what if Ayya recognizes your face from the poster
Correct
It will be good to have money..
Where do we go for money, if not for stealing?
Hey ! Don't tell me that we will steal!
We shouldn't take money away from those in need
But..... if we steal like the movie 'Gentleman'?
And rob the wicked?
The only evil rich man we know is Ayya
What if we steal from Ayya?
♪ (Jai Ho from Slumdog Millionaire) ♪
Hey Kodukkapuli...
In our whole village...
Even in our whole community...
I am the only one who drank with our family deity
If I say this... no one will believe it
Don't say shit, everyone will laugh out of their asses
Right! You are right
The whole world is like this..
...always laughing at the poor
Lets say there is a rich man...
He gets off a luxury car
His dhoti slips off....
What will people say?
'Oh no... the good man's dhoti has fallen down'
But if dhoti slips for people like us...
they will say 'Motherfucker, he can't even tie a dhoti'
Money is very important, Kodukkapuli
Then, why the fuck did you gamble it away?
I was deceived
Everyone tricked me
yeah, you are always like this
Not any more
We can earn back all that money in one phone call
Isn't it? What is it?
- Phone number is in the room dumbass
- Stop, I am coming too
Where is it dad?
We were talking right here
He also spoke about his 'cutie', remember?
Is it not here? did we lose it?
All is lost!
I knew it! Luck and us?
- Kodukkapuli
- Search you ass
Why?
One can oil the body and roll on the sand
...and you get only sand in return
The astrologer was right back then...
..'you will lose everything you have'
..'you won't get anything ... not a penney either'
Shut your hole and search
Hey ! I shouldn't tell you this
So many women lined up to marry me
Instead, I married your mom, why?
Fate
Nothing good ever
happens to me.
hey, move
It won't happen. I am a loser.
Is this it?
We found it?
I knew it. I knew it
You can get a thing, only if you keep repeating that you won't
Hello!   Is it him?  They were searching for you
It's you? Where is the powder?
Fucking whore! I don't like this town.
In morning, they killed the cock
Now, they are trying to kill us
No respect for aristocrats here
How much to ask?
What do you think?
It should be a bailout amount..
Let us ask ₹100,000
Fuck your father! That money won't stick
Why do you want to steal from others?
Greedy fellow...You are like your mom
How much is our debt? 5000
2000 for the cock
Another 1000 for stay and travel
Let us ask for 8000
Are you really an idiot or just act like one?
Hello, this is Kalaiyaan speaking. The stiff is with me.
Which stuff?
Whiteman's snuff. Bava lodge.
Haa
I am by the broken clock tower.
But I got no time. Hurry up.
Haa ?
Green dhoti. Sandal shirt. Blood all over it. A towel
You?
Red Maruti car?
Bring 200,000 with you
Ok Ok Ok
Haa  Hello
Don't forget to bring two lakhs................No mention..
What do you think now? Impressed ?
I am unmarried
I love tender coconut...
Sweet  ...  Sweet....
Hey Jokers, he is by the broken clock tower..... go..
But you have to accept a fact, Kodukkapuli
Your dad is smarter than my dad......ha.
Hey Kodukkapuli
We don't know if these folks are good or bad
What if they beat us and steal the stuff?
Oh yeah. You are smart for real.
Ha
You don't know a lot about your dad
Can you give me the bag?
Let me go hide this bag
If they show up, sternly say it to them..
'Show the money, have the honey'
Kodukkapuli, where are you hiding it?
- I won't tell. You are a blabber mouth
- All of him is poison. (lovingly)
Shit! The chasers at the lodge are in the Maruti car
(approaching car)
Dad!
Pa .... Pa..
Pa
My silver pistol is missing
Did you take it?
(Maruti van door opening)
No
(Van door locking)
I swear, I don't know
Him?
Small world........
Hello sir... (someone answering a phone call) Tell me sir...
Do you know English?
No.. No..
Aah..
I got a call that Pasupathy escaped from Mullu
If my guess is right...
Pasupathy will join Gajendran to cause trouble
If not, he will pull his loyal men to create a new gang
I have to ruin it somehow
Call Sub-Inspector Mayilvahanan
We have to "leak information" to Gajendran
That bitch won't believe, if it came directly from us
'Enemy's enemy is a friend'
.. it is Ayya's mantra
If my guess is right....
Sir, I have to meet Mullu at your police station?
Can you arrange that?
Hey, he won't show up
Why will Gajendran's man agree to meet Ayya's man?
Tell him it's Pasupathy, he will show up today
- ₹ 2000
- I will pay in the evening
Will you be alive till then? Ha... Ha .... Ha..
Ha
Hey Gajendran, how much cash do you got at hand?
- What the cunt-hair for?
- I have some good information for you
Clairvoyance, anyone..
May I palm read your future ?
I can read the past and the future
I think you don't believe me...swami
Swami ! Think of 2 flowers, let me read your palm only if I get them right..
Have you picked them? swami ?
Swami, There are flowers of different kind, color, smell
There is Lily, Lotus, Chrysanthemum and more
But they are not what you picked...swami
They are not daisy, water lily, chrysanthemum or ghanera .... swami
You thought of a white colored flower
And one in pink color
The two flowers you picked are...
Jasmine and Rose
Correct, Sir?
No........No.........
Swamy ! What are those two flowers you had picked?
Andy Flower and Grant Flower
- What is this shit?
- I told you earlier but no one believed
- He shot at me. But at blank point, he let Mullu live
- I am done with this shit
Gajapathy, this is the station. Can't kill anyone here
We saw them meet secretly. Let us hear what Mullu has to say
- Mullu, why are you late?
- It got late
Where? At the police station?
- What did you talk about?
- We spoke nothing
- How much did he offer?
- We didn't speak shit
- Why not?
- Because he is a dumb cunt
He had a chance to kill you, why didn't he?
I am asking you
I told you. Can't you understand the first time?
Are you that stupid?
He is paying the cop to meet you. Yet he said nothing?
Because he is a dumb cunt
He took your gun.. had it on your head...
Yet he shot at someone far away and not you?
Because he is a dumb cunt
Mullu...
..if I believe it, I am the dumb cunt
Do you think this is wrong?
Subbu, worm is eaten by fish, fish is eaten by man. It's life!
When you put it that way
Can we do it right?
Let me repeat our plan. See if it is good
When we go home, Ayya will be in a afternoon nap
Key will be under his pillow.
We will take the safe key out and get the bag
Lock it and leave the keys in the same spot Subbu!
That's your only responsibility
I will leave the bag at the corner shop
.. and tell him that 'We will get the bag later'
When Ayya wakes up, ask him that you want to see a movie.
Ayya wouldn't let you alone, so he will send me along
We will leave as if we are going to movies ...
- ... grab the bag and escape!
- Escape!
Movie is 3 hours. To and fro is 2 hours.
For 5 hours, Singaperumal won't look for us
By then, we would be in Andra
-  That's all
- easy
easy
Watch out Subbu, you know nothing
You are safe, because I was here
But you are always going to be with me
Subbu ! Did you notice that I called Ayya as 'Singaperumal'?
Fear is still there, but braveness has come
(Kaalaiyan crying in pain)
I really don't know
Where?
My son has hid it somewhere
Where is your son?
Where is he now?
Wherever you caught me...
..he is somewhere near by
I don't know where he is now
Hey !
Let him go
Ah!
This morning, you killed my fighting cock
I didn't take it personally
You didn't care I am an Aristocrat
You beat me up..... Haa
I didn't take it personally either
But let us stop everything here, OK?
ok ?
We can stop
But you are not telling me the truth
But I told everything I know
(Kaalaiyan crying out in pain)
I am really scared Subbu
What if we mess it up?
Let's drop all of it
Let us not see each other or talk
You are alive, that's enough for me
Don't want any of these plans
- Why Subbu?
- Listen to me, no!
If Ayya once....
just once...
...suspects a little bit
I don't care what happens to me, but you...
What were we thinking?
Who is he?
He controls the whole city
We are just some idiots.... fools
Subbu !
Let's not do this plan, please
Why Subbu?
Because I really love you a lot..
Sorry !  Sorry for everything...
hug me one last time.........please
But I don't like being here
Let us take a risk
Let's escape .........
Why?
Because I love you too
Scream of pain......
Whore!
Beat me now
Beat me
I got my son.. he will destroy you
He is smart.. he will destroy you ....
What the fuck is this shit?
We can't do anything for sometime
Is it our stuff?
Look at this village idiot's valor
10,000 lost on fucking nothing
Now, where to search for his son?
Why did you take my dad?
We told we were returning the powder
Wrong number
Hey yellow shirt, the call is for you
Hello ?
- Hey !  Which powder are you talking about?
- The one in Bava Lodge
- Where is that powder?
- It is with me
- Where are you?
- Let go of my dad, I will tell you
- I don't have your dad
- He spoke to you on phone
- To me? This number?
- Hmm
Do you have another number?
Should I call them?
Listen .. Listen ... Listen...........don't...don't..
Don't call them. If you do...
...they will take you too
Give the stuff to me, I will save your dad
How do I trust you?
Ok...
Whoever took your dad, took my wife too
Give the stuff to me...I will save your dad
You couldn't keep your wife safe...
..how are you going to save my dad?
Hell with you, then call them. They will take you too.
Do you have any other option?
That's why you are calling this number.
I will save him, not for you or your dad
..because I want my wife back..that's why
Don't call them
Will you?
I won't
OK.
Come to AK mills at 5
Do you know where it is?
It is near by, ask around
My name is Pasupathy
I am Kodukkapuli
What's with the on-time payments?
What did you speak with Mullu?
It's way more than I want
Sir, I need another help, keep it as advance
I am listening
The stuff everyone's looking for... I have it
Haa ?
I am ready to return it to Ayya..
...instead Kasthuri and a man called 'Kaalaiyan'
..ask for their release
Sir, I won't cause him trouble, neither should he
Only you can talk and make him compromise
Why don't you speak?
Ask me to beat up 4, I can...
...I can't think and speak
I said something this morning and it has gone this far
Sir,  I know you can make it happen
Ok, give me your phone
Use your phone, I will pay for it
Why are you talking like that?
Haa ..
Hey !  At 5:30, Pasupathy will bring the stuff to AK mills...
Go take it
What?
I am thinking
What are you thinking? 'Thinking-ka-baal'
As in, what do with Pasupathy?
Kiss and make out with him
Go kill him. Leave!
Hey !
At least this time, do the job right!
And don't bring his mom or gradmom this time
I don't want them
Go, do it!
♪ (Vaa vaa pakkam vaa from Thanga Magan) ♪
Hey ! Call me if Marwari seth comes. I Have to return the cash...
Its good to get the stuff .... and don't pay for it....
He is awake, how do we do that?
The money will be gone when Marwari seth comes by.
Before Ayya finishes showering...
...can you drop off the bag at the shop?
Please we won't get another chance
Hey Subbu, pick up the phone bitch..
Hello...... Hello....
Who?
Got disconnected
Beautiful
Wonderful
Marvelous
- Sure its OK?
- Take it out
That's it!
Hurry up
What if Ayya asks about me?
OK. I will make an excuse
Wait a minute
I am scared
- Why do we need that?
- Just in case. Keep it
Be careful..Keep an eye out.
Bye..bye..
Why are you late? Where is the powder?
Where is my dad?
I told you I will get him. Go fetch it. Go!
Hey ! I told you. Go get it.
Show my dad, only then I will give it.
Is your dad with me?  Haa ?
Listen. Give me powder. I will exchange that for your dad. Go
Then why will I give it to you? I will give it to them
Hay ... Hay... Hay...
You little prick. Fucking my patience.. I will kill you.
Why can't you understand?
Go..
I am gonna trust you. Don't betray me
- Hey ! You stay here
- I will come with you
- Where is my dad?
- These guys are different
If you think I am a little boy, I will cut you up
If I don't get my dad, I will murder you.
If I don't get my dad,
I will murder you.
Give the bag, I will take care
I will get your dad, like I told you
Stay here
Gajendran
A lot have gone wrong between us
I will return the goods back to you. Lets not fight
Gajapathy, you get this
I will explain the problem, you will understand
- Gajapathy
- First, I will check the goods. We can cut him after
I wanted to do quick business, but I messed it up. Sorry!
Do you ever think before acting? Dumb cunt
Gajapathy
There is thin line between Idiot and genius..
.. I am crossing that line now
I pissed off Ayya
But he is a heavy weight
I can do anything against him alone
I need another heavy weight for that
Gajendran is a heavy weight, but..
..he was pissed off too
If Gajendran gets psychotic mad, he will annihilate
But he doesn't get angry like Gajapathy
I will have to mess with him... to make him do what I need
Think. Think. Think.
My first step - Mullu
Why am I here, if you are not talking? Dumb cunt!
That triggered Gajendran. Now he is angry
But not angry enough...
Step 2 - To get Gajendran and Gajapathy with the gang
... to a place of my choosing
..you can make it happen..
Hello Gajendran
If he said 5:30, we should be there early..before Ayya's men
My last step - Gajapathy
Now... Gajendran is maniac mad
Anger is blinding his eyes
Why I tried so hard to make Gajendran...
... so mad at me ?   WHY?
For this!
Brother, they are here
Singaperumal, you son of a whore
Kill them all
Pasupathy and Singaperumal have been playing me
Why did I was certain that they will end up fighting?
Enemy's enemy is a friend. True...
But more importantly...
...they both are still enemies
Hey Subbu...
Who was on the phone?
Haa !
(kitchen utensils clanging)
Subbu
Subbu... Sappa...
Where is the bag?
Where is Sappa?
Where is Suppa?
I don't know
Hay Hay! Sappa escaped with the bag full of money.... go..
Go. Catch him. Kill him..
Hay !  Sappa ran with the money, find him!
Go .....Go.........Go..
Where did you go?
Madam asked to buy fruits
Where is the money?
Where is the bag?
Sappa bitch! Tell me
Are you looking for this?
You are trying to kill me?
What you feared is true, Subbu...
Did you mess it up Subbu?
No, I didn't
Make her cry somehow.... ..Console her ......and then screw her!
What if we steal from our Ayya?
I am scared Subbu
If we mess it up?
Lets drop all plans
- Lets risk it Subbu
- Why?
Because I love you too
Just in case. Keep it
Hey! Sobbu..
Everyone thinks he is a looser..
But actually he is the real Don !
Fucking Joker !
Sappa shot Ayya?
So you killed Sappa for that?
You have suffered a lot here..
I will take care. Leave
Ayya, tell me
This is not Ayya....Pasupathy
Singaperumal tried to kill me
Now, he is not alive
I killed Gajendran
Killed Gajapathy
Nagaraj is out of picture too
Now on, it's just me
I know you did this for Ayya
I am not angry at you
But, Kasthuri needs to be here... now
Take him to the hospital
- Do you love your dad so much?
- Not like that
But he is my dad
Had any problem?
What happened to the money?
Sappa hid it somewhere ..
That dog is dead now
Thank you so much
- How is Ayya doing?
- He is very good
Someone who will listen to me
Someone to blame for the money
I needed an Idiot for that
He was Sappa
Poor looser? Not really.. he is innocent
Just like he said...
'Worm, fish, man...life is like that'
As far as I am concerned, Sappa is just another man...
All men are sappa (Looser) too
The best thing about being woman is ... its a man's world.
Watch out Subbu, you know nothing
You are safe, because I was here
Idiot
NagaDutta : Vishnugupta, what is dharma?
Vishnugupta Chankya : Dharma is doing what is necessary